So anyway, why did Goemon decide
to get married after all?
Isn't it natural? Why don't you
try settling down yourself?
Oh, is that a proposal? Fujiko,
how much dowry are you offering?
How 'bout this?
Lupin, do you smell that?
No, not that!
Yeah, something smells fishy around here.
And now, we shall commence
the ceremony of the Shuujoo Vase,
the legacy of the Suminawa family.
From the moment you are given this vase
you will cease to exist as Goemon
of the Ishikawa Clan
and shall be reborn as Goemon
of the Suminawa Clan.
Receive it with reverence, and see that it
is handed down for generations to come.
Who're you?!
G-Goemon, the vase!
G-Give it back, damn you!
Give it up!
They're gonna break the vase!
Don't let 'em get away!
No!
Hold it!
What's all that commotion?
They're coming this way, Fujiko!
Okay!
What's this?
Wh-Where's the vase?
Oh, uh, this one?
No!
Damn!
D 51, 1:00 Tomorrow Night
What the hell is this?
The Fuma Conspiracy
Lupin the Third
Whimsical, cute, spoiled...
I've heard the talk
A bouquet, caviar, a limousine, dancing...
A pick-up phone call
C'est la vie!
I'm a little bored of life
I could use some excitement
Suddenly we touch glasses, and you say I'm like you
A smile, clouded eyes, they've touched my heart
Ah! I didn't expect to fall in love
Just who are you?
I love you so much it makes me dizzy
Even though I've always kept my cool
Oh, I'm not used to being in love
The universe is trying to tell me I'll get hurt
Whimsical, cute, spoiled...
So long as I have you
Bouquets, caviar, limousines, dancing...
I won't need any of that
Oh, I don't want to beg
I'm far beyond that
This may be love, the wind whispers
Here Lies
Lupin
Would you please come
back, Inspector?
Will you give it up?
I witnessed Lupin's final moments.
Now that Lupin has met
his demise, I've lost my purpose.
Inspector, do you really think
that Lupin is dead?
Yeah. I've been intoning sutras every day
so that the poor guy's soul will rest in peace.
This is a photo taken around noon today,
during a robbery here in Hida.
If Lupin is really dead, then who in
the world is the man in this photo?
No way...
Has there been any information since?
No, nothing yet!
I am very sorry. Murasaki
hasn't been found yet.
Maybe we should give them the vase—
Goemon...
Please, don't worry about
Murasaki anymore.
What?! What are you trying to say?
As you know, our ancestors created gadgets.
They were renowned throughout the land
since the time when taxes were first
levied in Japan, in the 7th Century.
On one occasion, using all their skills,
they concealed a treasure meant
for us, their descendants
and put it deep beneath
the surface of the earth.
And in that vase is...
the key to the treasure?
Suminawa, could it be that you
know who those intruders are?
Please tell me! Who were they?
The Fuma Clan.
Fuma?
The gang who struck were agents of the Fuma.
They have sought this vase for the past 400 years,
and we've fought to keep it from them.
In other words, they're bandits.
I cannot abide anyone who calls himself
a thief, whoever he may be.
Don't you agree, Goemon?
Jeez! Such harsh language!
But you know, this is getting kinda interesting.
What do we do, Lupin? He said "treasure."
Well, by the Lupin philosophy,
the babe obviously comes first!
Figures. Oh boy, here we go again.
The successive heads of our house have
posessed this vase for generations.
They've protected it with their lives.
I understand you love Murasaki,
but if you are to carry on our family legacy,
you must keep the vase from them at all costs.
But this concerns Murasaki's—
Please, let that sink in.
It looks like just another vase to me.
This is a "Million Ryo" treasure. No
way is this just an ordinary vase.
A million ryo? Let me see it!
How do you know?
Oh, I just hoped it'd be that much.
Shoot.
Jigen, hold still!
Leave this to us, Goemon.
We can get a vase like that back
any day of the week, see?
Thank you.
All you have left, a memory
Picture of you spying on me
Searching your heart, right from the start...
I knew that no one would love me like you do...
All you have left's a photo
Image of you spying on me
Searching your soul, you didn't know...
I never would go away...
I'll recover, you're my lover...
They will never separate us...
Please know your secrets, they're safe with me...
Kiss me but I'll never tell...
So that's how it was.
Goemon, you stud!
Damn, we wish we could
be in your shoes!
Right, Jigen?
I guess.
If this means you're settling down,
I guess you'll be leaving the gang?
That's too bad.
Yikes, this is awful! It's Zenigata!
Inspector, I was appointed
to this post just last month.
Right now, I'm in charge of the Lupin case.
You're in charge of Lupin?
So you claim Lupin will
indeed show up?
Absolutely, sir. Let's charge him
with kidnapping this woman!
You'll get the Chief's good graces for this!
Gifu Prefecture Police
Is he gone yet?
Kazami, slow down a bit.
I saw something weird. Slow down!
Wait, Lupin? Get back down!
Lupin! You're under arrest!
You aren't getting away this time!
How can you say that? I haven't done anything!
Hey, let's beat it.
Sure thing!
Hut!
You won't get away!
Better watch out. See?
Hey! Hold it, Lupin!
Hold it, Lupin!
After him!
Bye-bye!
Don't let him get away!
Jigen, isn't that a path to the river?
We going for you-know-what?
All right!
Get 'em!
All right, charge!
B-But—
Just do it!
Show me what you got!
Hey! You're going to sink at this rate!
Shut up! Full throttle!
Didn't I tell you? What
a tragic loss this is.
May your soul rest in peace.
All right, let's get to it Jigen!
That scared the pants off me! I wonder if
they've souped-up that car or something.
Whoa! Stop! This way!
Hold it! Stop!
Hold it, Lupin!
There! There!
Lupin! Stop!
I won't let you get away now!
You're mine, Lupin!
Hey! Go! Keep going!
Thank you for your trouble! See you later!
What now, Inspector?
This is all because of your terrible driving, moron!
Is this the right place?
Yeah. It's just ahead of us.
Bet it's been like this for ages!
Lupin, are you really gonna hand
that vase over to those guys?
Of course! I don't know how important this
vase is, but it ain't worth a life!
Right, Goemon?
Look! There it is!
Awesome! Feels like a steam locomotive museum.
That one?
Looks like it.
Welcome! You better have brought the vase with you.
You with the vase, come forward!
Give us Murasaki first!
No chance!
First we verify whether the vase
is the real thing or not.
I refuse! This is the real vase, and I'm not moving until you bring Murasaki out!
As you can see, she's fine.
Hand over the vase.
Murasaki... Murasaki comes first!
Don't move!
I don't trust that the vase isn't a fake.
Damn you!
If you're so unwilling to trust him,
don't blame me if it breaks.
Up it goes!
Voilà!
See! Again!
Again! Woops!
What are you doing?!
This vase is Murasaki's life!
Don't handle it so haphazardly!
Bring Murasaki to the center of the roundhouse.
We'll make the exchange there.
I don't think they're gonna return her to us.
Why don't we come back another time?
Quiet!
Goemon, or whatever your name is,
we'll trust you. Put the vase on
that end of the roundhouse!
We'll put the girl on this end.
Just so you know, if the vase turns
out to be a fake, you're all history!
And Lupin, or whatever your name is,
don't even think about doing anything stupid.
We'll see.
We'll let you score one for now,
but next time you may not be so lucky.
Did you think we'd give it up that easily?
Fire!
All right, let's see who can get to the treasure first.
This is getting exciting!
Goemon, did you really give up
our family treasure to save me?
I'll get it back. I promise.
Lupin! You're all surrounded!
Resistance is useless! Come out with your hands up!
Inspector, we've sealed off
the area in all directions!
They're backup from Aichi Prefectural Police!
Who told you to send for backup? Don't
do things you're not asked to!
I see, so that's the ticket.
Hey, Jigen! You're up!
I'm coming!
After 'em! After 'em!
Move it!
Suminawa
So this is the Fuma hideout.
Kazama Group, Ltd.
I've got a change of clothes back there.
Pick out whatever you like.
Okay.
So Goemon, what did you
want to talk to us about?
Murasaki is determined to come with me.
She's feeling responsible, I bet.
She wants to help you out. How sweet!
Why won't you stop her?!
Forget that! It's not our job!
Why don't you tell it to her straight?
And, another thing
What lies ahead of us
has nothing to do with you.
I want you to keep your hands off the treasure!
We can't do that! We've come too far!
Besides! We're the only ones who know
where we'll run into those Fuma bastards!
Tell me.
You gotta be kidding me. You
think that Lupin, the worlds greatest thief—
would run away when he's this close to the treasure?
And you won't budge on that?
Bingo!
Hey, Goemon!
Please...
Thanks for waiting!
Wow, that looks so good on you Murasaki!
Well Goemon, shall we get going?
W-Wait
Murasaki, how should I put this
Oh, the hiding place of the treasure?
Don't worry. I know where it is.
What?
Lupin told me about it just a while ago.
Later!
Murasaki, we'll see you again at Shakujoodake!
Sure!
By the way, I haven't seen Fujiko
around. What happened to her?
Don't worry about her.
I've planted a little gizmo
in Fujiko's pendant.
The analysis is complete, Boss.
And where is the treasure hidden?
In the Shinto shrine at the base of Shakujoodake.
Oh, I see!
Oh my, what a beautiful guest we have!
What brings you here?
Nothing. I was just out on an evening stroll.
I see. They're evidently
doing wonders for your health.
Now then,
we have some business to attend to,
so let us postpone our introduction.
Oh, don't mind me.
Looking for this?
Sure, you can have it back.
What're you doing?!
Now you've got it back!
A transmitter? Lupin!
Yamataka
Police Station
Be aware of your surroundings.
Yamataka
Police Station
Be aware of your surroundings.
Yamataka
Police Station
Be aware of your surroundings.
Yamataka
Police Station
Be aware of your surroundings.
Yamataka
Police Station
Be aware of your surroundings.
Yamataka
Police Station
Be aware of your surroundings.
Yamataka
Police Station
Dark out?
Be aware of your surroundings.
Yamataka
Police Station
Dark out?
Be aware of your surroundings.
Yamataka
Police Station
Dark out?
Be aware of your surroundings.
Police Station
Dark out?
Be aware of your surroundings.
Police Station
Dark out?
Be aware of your surroundings.
Police Station
Dark out?
Be aware of your surroundings.
Police Station
Dark out?
Be aware of your surroundings.
Police Station
Dark out?
Be aware of your surroundings.
Police Station
Dark out?
Be aware of your surroundings.
Police Station
Dark out?
Be aware of your surroundings.
Police Station
Dark out?
Be aware of your surroundings.
Did you find Lupin yet?
Not yet? Don't come
back here 'til you find him!
Damn you, Lupin!
Inspector!
Inspector! It's Lupin!
What?
Oops, overshot.
You sure this is it?
Supposedly.
Yamataka
Police Station
Did Fujiko get caught or something?
Yamataka
Police Station
What do we do?
Yamataka
Police Station
What do you think we're gonna do?
Yamataka
Police Station
Lupin! You're under arrest!
What a pain in the ass!
Damn it!
Stop it! What do you think you're doing?
Hey Pops, wanna know
something interesting?
Try frisking that fella. I bet that
Fujiko's pendant will pop up.
Hey you with the glasses! Didn't we meet at the wedding?
In addition to being a thief, are you
also moonlighting as a cop?
Kazami, what's this all about?
This is what it's all about, Inspector.
Later Pops!
See you next time!
Damn it! All units, move out!
Say, Mr. Guard, do me a favor...
Please, my back is itchy!
Could you scratch it for me, please?
Hey, come on. It's itchy!
It's so itchy. I can't stand it!
Is there something there?
My back is itchy. Maybe my bra's too tight.
Hey, take a look. It's itchy!
All right, if you say so.
It's further down, take a look.
But there's nothing—
So sorry.
Oh?
Whoops.
Watch it!
Knock it off!
Way to go!
Roger, stay on his tail!
I'll head over there as soon as I arrest Lupin!
Lupin! Hold it! Stop!
Aren't you supposed to arrest that impostor first?
Look how you made us go
so far out of our way!
Whoa!
Closed to traffic
What?!
Got you!
There!
There they are! After them!
Stop! Stop!
It's the police!
Charge!
Excuse us! After 'em!
Pervert!
Charge!
You're kidding!
There they are!
...and that's for the Pine Room—
Hold it!
Get them!
Lupin, give up and prepare to be arrested!
What a persistent old fart he is! Jeez!
You'll be sorry if you interfere!
Did you figure out who Kazami really is?
I know he's a Fuma, at least!
Then here's your evidence!
What's this?
He's a handful, isn't he?
Lose him in the smoke?
Get outta the way!
Wow, that's bright!
What the—
I've got you now, Lupin!
You can't get away from me now, damn you!
What?!
Later, Pops! Take care!
Damn it! You tricked me!
Oh my god!
Damn you! Damn you! Damn you!
I'll get you for this, Lupin!
There doesn't seem to be anything
out of the ordinary here, Boss.
Wait.
We don't know what kind of traps may be in place.
Use extreme caution!
What's next?
The map on the vase ends here.
I guess we'll just have to go in and see.
So you've come, after all.
But I won't let any of you take
even one step inside. Leave!
Sir, I am very pleased to see you so healthy,
but you'd live longer had you stayed home.
Ha! I've already given up living!
Prepare yourself!
Get off of me!
I see that you're all alone.
Now that it's come to this, you have only two choices.
Show us the way in or meet your end.
Kill me, then!
Who would wanna show you the way?!
If that is your wish...
It's Goemon and Murasaki!
Scatter!
Hold on. Let me rest for a moment.
We're almost there. You can do this, Murasaki.
Are you mad at me?
No, not at all!
I just want to make sure the Fuma doesn't get—
Am I a bother?
Of course not!
Do you mean it?
Yes, I mean it.
We've only been able to get this far
thanks to you, and I'm grateful.
Are you really?
A-Absolutely.
Then give me a sign of your gratitude.
Come on. Come on.
What's the matter?
Seems the Fuma have already gone inside.
What?
Murasaki, are you hurt?
Just a little startled.
Goemon...
I see. This would've led to nowhere.
Wait, my ancestors were known
for building clever gadgets.
I bet there's something set up in here.
Let's get going.
Watch your step. There might be
more traps set up.
There!
Lupin's gotta be around here somewhere!
Get busy!
Yes sir!
Binoculars!
Sir!
Great, now they're trapped like mice!
Are you all set? Follow me!
Yes sir!
Damn you, Lupin!
Looks like that impostor and the Lupin gang
are searching for treasure.
Dig to your heart's content!
This is government land!
Any treasure you dig up will be confiscated
by the Treasury Department
and used to reduce taxes!
Let's go!
Inspector! There's someone down there!
Say what?
Oh, wow!
Golden statues of the Twelve
Guardians of the Buddha of healing!
So this is the treasure!
No, I don't think so.
What?
These are nothing but wooden
statues covered with gold foil.
They're appreciable as art, but
hardly worth the Fumas' time.
Oh, what a bummer.
I get it!
I get it! Goemon, I get it!
It's where they're looking!
What?
Where does it look like the Twelve
Guardians are all looking?
Right here!
This is where the exit must be hidden!
You're right.
There's no sign that the Fuma has been here.
Let's go back, Murasaki!
Goemon—
Shhh!
Lupin!
H-Howdy, Goemon!
No! I must've missed them somewhere!
Lupin, where's the vase?
The vase? Oh, the vase...
The thing is, Fujiko kind of, well...
Uh, sorry!
she broke it!
What?!
She couldn't help it!
She got captured by those Fuma
dudes, and went through hell—
Unforgivable!
Wait, please!
Murasaki...
Don't get upset.
Not over one lousy vase. We've come this far.
But—
She's right.
Seeing as how the Fuma have gotten this
far, the vase has no value anymore.
Don't you think we should focus on
beating the Fuma to the treasure?
The Fuma, huh?
Come on, Goemon...
So the vase no longer has value?
No, no,
the value of the vase is not just in the map.
In fact, there's a golden key embedded
in the bottom of the vase.
Unless the key
is used to unlock the hidden
lock within that small shrine...
The entire cavern will collapse
an hour from now, you say?
Along with everyone inside, and the treasure.
Mister! Who has the key now?!
No matter who has it now, it's already too late.
I shot out the lock, you see.
That's murder!
You just killed them!
Mister, do you even realize
your granddaughter is in there?
Murasaki?
What? What's happened to Murasaki?
Tell me! Tell me!
Please calm down!
I said, your granddaughter is in there!
Oh, it's a dead-end.
Maybe we took a wrong turn somewhere?
That we don't know yet.
Lupin!
You all right, Lupin?
I'm fine, but...
Don't look!
Damn! This is a little gross for a guidepost.
Let's get going, at any rate.
Hey.
Goemon, looks like you're up.
This looks like a Nightingale Floor.
Nightingales ain't the only thing gonna
be singing, that's for sure.
There's a passage here!
It could be just a decoy.
But I don't see anything else resembling a path.
That settles that.
What the hell is this?
Nothing but holes.
Which one is the real passage?
Looks like we'll have to split up and search.
Oh, brother. Which is the real exit?
Oops! Here we go!
There must've been a cave-in somewhere!
We can't use guns, then.
It's open!
What happened?
A portion of the rear appears to have caved in, sir!
Lupin!
L-Lemme go!
It's not safe!
A man must help another man!
If we don't do something, they'll all be killed!
It's too dangerous! It's like a maze inside!
Inspector! I will show you the way.
If we don't hurry, we'll never make it.
I can't expose a civilian to danger.
Please! Let me show you the
way! And save Murasaki...
All right! Very well!
You're in the way! Move it!
Get out of the way!
Man, this can't be for real!
All the paths have caved in!
Goemon!
This must be it.
Hey Lupin! This looks like a passage,
but it's all blocked up.
So then this way?
Looks like the Fuma have been here.
No choice but to go in, then.
Goemon! Are you all right? Goemon!
Yo, Goemon! What's wrong?
What is it? Everything all right?
What's with him?
I don't know.
Goemon!
What's going on here?
Now, hold it!
Hallucinogenic gas!
Hey! Jigen!
Wh-What is it?
Just get out!
Go, you two! Right now!
No! Stay away!
No, Goemon!
Goemon!
Lupin!
Cheer up, Goemon.
You were under the influence of the gas.
We found a path ahead, Lupin.
But if we don't hurry, the Fuma will beat us.
They've gotta be pretty close.
All right!
Don't worry. We'll catch up soon.
All right, then.
Fujiko! Watch out for hidden gadgets!
Okay!
Damn! This is something else!
A million ryo doesn't even come close!
Wait, stop! Fujiko!
I've been dreaming of this moment!
I love you! I love you!
Fujiko, be careful!
Oh, yes! Gold! It's all mine!
Man, this is unbelievable!
Yo Lupin, why are you looking so gloomy?
Something's off.
What is?
Where have the Fuma gone off to?
Huh?
Lupin!
Sorry, Lupin.
So you're Lupin? I was beginning
to think you weren't coming.
Yo! You're the Boss?
A pleasure to meet you.
Let's talk business. Since there's
so much treasure in here,
why don't we split it even?
That ain't a bad deal.
Don't move!
What do you mean by that?
I've planted a bomb, and this is it's switch.
We'll be all buried in here!
If it's real.
Wanna try it and see?
Would you get off me!
Now, clear out!
Don't move!
The games are over. Die!
Lupin!
Now!
Right!
Don't let them get away!
Bye!
What the hell's this?!
They're coming!
We're done for if they
make it up this ladder, Lupin!
I know.
Take this!
Lupin!
Looks like another empty bomb threat... Huh?
What's happening, Gakusha?!
Stay back!
You all right, Lupin?
Man, that's potent stuff!
I kept one for myself. I'm sure that I'll
be seen as a real beauty if I use it.
What're you talking about? Your true self will
come out, and you'll be seen as a monster!
What?
Let's go!
Murasaki...
Oh, damn it all!
Come on up, Goemon.
I'll let you catch a wonderful show!
Stop.
Drop your sword.
Hey.
Stop right there.
It's too bad, seeing how far you've had to climb, but now you must jump off.
Guarantee Murasaki's safety.
Fine.
Come on! Get on with it!
What's the matter? Feeling scared?
Goemon...
Forgive me Goemon!
Murasaki!
Goemon!
Another earthquake!
Get outta here, Lupin!
What?
Everybody, get out of here!
Murasaki!
This place has been rigged to collapse! Move it!
Grandpa!
Lupin!
Run! Hurry!
Run, Fujiko!
No way!
Hurry!
Collapse? This treasure?
Just when our 400 year-long dream
is about to be realized?
This gold is mine! I will hand it over to no one!
My gold...
Hurry! Jump!
Lupin!
Here I go!
Inspector!
Why you!
Inspector! Inspector!
Over here! Over here!
Inspector!
Good work! Everybody, run for it!
Everybody, move it!
Where's Lupin? Where's Lupin's gang?
You didn't see Lupin come out?
No, nobody!
They couldn't be buried in there!
Inspector, over there!
Here.
There was a shortcut? After—
Let them go. They didn't take anything.
I can charge him with interfering with
police officers, traffic violations,
and destruction of pottery!
Lupin, you're under arrest!
But it's too bad. We almost had all that treasure!
I got a little.
Just this one shingle, though.
Great!
I'll take that as part of my dowry.
I still wanna enjoy the single life for the time being.
You should settle down soon!
I'll think about it. Later!
Hey, how about we split it between us?
Damn! You greedy wench!
Let's get going, Jigen!
Goemon's not here yet.
Anyways Lupin, could you
get your feet out of my face?
No. I must undergo training to
remedy all of my weaknesses.
Only then can I return to you.
Please forgive me!
But...
I'm sorry.
I knew it!
I'm not going to wait for you!
Well then Murasaki, see you around!
Lupin's headed toward Takayama!
Make sure you get on him!
Grandpa, shall we go?
Yeah. He's a free spirit. He'll
be back before you know it.
It just takes a bit of patience.
You know that, right?
Sure!