Yor's secret identity...
Briar Rose.
This time, you'll be protecting the client.
Yor had been given one of her tallest orders yet:
to protect the head of the mafia
from numerous assassins.
Meanwhile,
We have a winner!
Anya won first place in a raffle,
and the Forgers all happened to
end up on the same cruise ship.
Many assassins had already snuck aboard.
Sickle-and-Chain Barnaby?!
What should I do?
The last thing I need is for this to escalate!
The lady from the circus is so cool!
Nice, Anya!
Anya did her best to make sure Loid
didn't find out Yor's true identity.
This was the most exciting
and valiant adventure yet!
Could you be any lamer?
Yor was able to narrowly avoid
the enemy's attacks.
What am I doing this for?
I've found you.
And during the fireworks show,
Yor had to go head-to-head
against multiple assassins.
All I wanted was to protect his innocence.
And I stand by that.
In fact, I have more to lose than ever before.
I'm sure Loid would appreciate this.
He'd understand.
I have no reason...
to give up!
The fireworks were so pretty!
I'm glad you enjoyed them.
It's a shame that we couldn't find Yor, though.
The ship is just too big.
Shock!
I totally forgot about Mommy!
I need to find her, quick!
The State Security officers seem uneasy.
What's going on?
"Gather personnel quickly..."
"...has been set in a room..."
A bomb at the bottom of the ship?!
Say what now?!
But who set it? And why?
What should I do? Gather more information?
No, the State Security
officers will take care of this.
Trying to intervene would be
extremely risky.
On the other hand, there are
countless lives at stake.
I can't just ignore this
considering the greater risk at hand.
But I also can't leave Anya alone.
What should I do?
Daddy!
I wanna keep playing!
Hey...
Seriously? Right now?
I'm gonna go play in there.
You go back to our room!
A daycare center? Perfect timing.
All right. I'll come get you in a bit,
then. Just stay right here.
Okie dokie.
Please take good care of my daughter.
Her name is Anya.
Of course!
Wow, I get to play with a ball!
Okay, now's my chance.
All right, then.
What should we play with, Anya?
I'm playing with this ball.
You sure are. You're amazing!
Gonna be bored with it soon, though.
And I'm bored.
Right, I guess that's enough of that.
I wanna draw now.
Sure.
Just one second.
Okay, what would you like to draw?
Huh?
Anya?
Well? Can you disarm it?
Shut up! I'm trying to concentrate.
We're counting on you. There are some
really important people on this ship.
Just shut up already!
I heard there was a bomb in this area.
Oh, it's right over there.
Pardon my intrusion.
I used to be in the navy.
It was my job to dismantle
and dispose of explosives.
I'd like to offer my assistance.
Is it possible to move it away from here?
You can't. It's rigged to blow.
A time bomb, type B-CP62.
A bomb that extremists
from the West love using.
Were they after a high-profile Eastern official?
Or the ship as a whole?
No, HQ would've told me about any
ongoing extremist operations.
It's possible the bomb was designed
to look like the West was responsible.
Hey, what's the matter?
Think you can deal with it?
No problem at all.
I'll help Mommy while he's dealing with the bomb!
Where is she?
To think she slaughtered
all those well-known assassins.
What a terrifying woman.
There's a bad guy here!
It's definitely time to go.
I've made more than enough from this job.
I'm getting the hell outta here
before the hyenas start circling.
You guys can keep squabbling
for what time you have left.
The front of the ship?
Soon enough, this whole ship will be underwater.
And they'll all be clueless
until it's too late.
I lost the bad guy!
It doesn't matter. Now,
I need to focus on finding Mommy!
The roof toward the front!
That's... Mommy's stabby thing!
This isn't working!
I can't get close enough
to him to finish him off!
Mommy's up there!
She's fighting without her stabby thing?!
I can't hear her from here.
I need to climb up somehow...
I can't!
I gotta save Mommy!
Reach her!
Rising Hope!
Quit making all that noise!
It wasn't me! I dunno what that was.
If that nutcase finds us, we're done for!
You think I don't know that?
We gotta strike now while she's distracted!
Gretcher is completely defenseless right now!
How much longer do you think
we'll be down here?
Once we kill them,
we're getting the hell outta here!
Let's go!
Exactly as planned.
Gunshots from behind?!
That's my—
Come.
I'm going to end this with my next strike.
You're done for.
You've left yourself completely open!
You bastard...
What happened to Mommy's battle?
It's finally over... I'm so tired.
She won! And she couldn't have done it without me.
I need to let Olka and the others out.
He successfully disarmed it!
Well done!
It was nothing.
I'm far more nervous about
being surrounded by so many
State Security officers than the bomb.
What's the matter?
Farewell, Princess Lorelei.
It'll be nice listening to their cries
as I drift away.
But where did this come from?
Was someone trying to help?
Oh, no! I must withdraw!
Maybe it was the wind.
Director! Are you all right?
There are still multiple bombs?!
If the suspect's goal is to sink this ship,
the amount of gunpowder here
is nowhere near enough.
We should call for an evacuation...
To where, exactly?!
We don't even know how many bombs
there are or where they are!
Besides, the guest list is full
of important people.
We can't cause a commotion!
They're trying to save face.
You know what'll happen if
you blab any of this, don't you?
Gather available men
to search the rest of the ship.
That goes for the crew, too.
Don't let the higher-ups figure
out what you're doing!
I need to hurry back before
the caretaker gets suspicious!
This hurts so fucking bad!
I need to get this thing out of me.
I can't fight in this state.
I've got to figure out a new plan.
I'm not stopping 'til they're dead!
A bad guy!
What'd you just say to me?
Wait, is that...
a bomb?!
There's a bomb inside the clock?
So that wasn't the only bomb
that Daddy had to deal with?!
Could it be that bastard?
Tch.
Oh, no! I need to tell Daddy!
But I don't know where he is anymore!
Even if I was able to tell him,
he'd figure out my secret!
How am I supposed to find a bomb around here?!
They told me to search the lower decks,
but that's so vague it's practically useless!
Pardon me.
Huh? Can I help you?
Earlier, I saw a weird old guy stick a bom—
a boogie onto that clock.
That's real gross, so please clean it.
A booger? Sorry miss, but I'm busy.
Shock!
Wait, information about some weirdo
is exactly what I'm looking for.
I mean, it's not very likely,
but I guess it couldn't hurt to check.
Okay, I'll take a look.
Seriously...
Those fireworks were amazing, weren't they?
Pardon me, sir.
Tomorrow, we'll be on the island...
Hear 'em loud and clear.
Don't push yourself too much, Director.
Sounds like the bodyguard won.
Hold on a sec' there, mister.
Where do you think you're
going all by your lonesome?
Great to see you, too.
You're the one who planted
the bombs, aren't you?
You were planning to take
all of us out with them?
Yeah, and what are you going to do about it?
This is the perfect opportunity to kill
all targets in one fell swoop.
I told you some of the client's
guests were on that ship, too!
Not like any of them are important.
Don't worry. The bombs are made to
look like they were made in the West.
If things go well, war will break out again,
and weapon sales will be through the roof.
The client will be plenty happy.
Whatever.
Get this boat moving. We're starting from square one.
Who the hell said I'd give you a ride?
There's only enough food and water for myself.
Is that right? I guess I won't be sharing, then.
Bombs have been located
in the third cargo room,
the upper part of the balance tank,
and the boiler room.
Right. Yes.
From what you're describing, it sounds like
all the bombs were
planted by the same person.
Please be careful of the trap
I mentioned and proceed with caution.
Okay, on to the next one.
Huh?!
The upper floors... on the eighth deck, too?!
Here it is.
With all these people around?
Their goal isn't just to sink the ship?
We're just doing some
maintenance on the clock here.
We need to get these people away—
No. There's probably no time for that.
What should I do?!
We're just conducting some inspections!
Uh, hello?!
I'm going to go throw this into the ocean!
What?!
I'll treat you to a little performance
before I off you.
We're about to witness the goriest
firework show of a lifetime.
You'll be able to enjoy
the symphony of agonized screams
from the wiretaps throughout the ship.
Hey! Wait! That clock is an antique!
Whew, that was close.
Hm? Was there something down there?
What was that noise?
More fireworks?
Could you make some kind of
announcement so there's no commotion?
Understood...
Yay!
He saved the day!
Which he couldn't have done without me.
I found you!
How dare you wander off like that?!
I-I'm sorry!
I-It's because I was about
to poop my pants...
Then you should've just said so!
We're heading back!
Wait! There are still bombs we haven't dealt with!
Well, why didn't you just say so?
Let's head to the bathroom, then!
Thoroughly inspect each section,
including the upper floors.
It's possible there are still
terrorists on board.
Please request that State Security
be on guard around the clock.
Y-Yes, sir!
I thought I just heard some faint explosions.
Some of them may still remain.
Stay on your guard.
All right. We're all set.
It's a bit early, but let's lower the boat.
Until the cruise ship gets far enough,
please stay covered with this cloth.
All right.
I wish you the best of luck!
Thank you... so much.
Wait, your clothes are going to
get dirty! There's blood—
He wants a hug goodbye, too.
Oh, I really shouldn't. My hands are quite dirty...
Those hands are the reason
he has a future to begin with.
He's so warm.
This might be naïve of me,
and maybe I should mind my own business,
but still...
I pray that you find true peace
and harmony with your family.
It seems like the coast is clear.
Now we just have to wait for
word from the retrieval ship.
Remain vigilant until the dawn breaks—
Stop letting yourself become sentimental.
Remember that we are nothing
more than foot soldiers.
I-I'm sorry!
By the way...
I forgot I had a message for you.
Forger wants to make plans
for the resort tomorrow.
Loid and Anya?
Oh, but—
I'll be on the lookout for any stragglers.
As a reward for completing this
mission, see their request through.
Make sure you ice your face so
they don't see the swelling.
Also,
don't let them see what happened
to your chest.
O-Of course!
I'll wear something that covers it!
Miraculously, I was able to
ensure everyone's safety.
I'm sure I can leave the rest
to the State Security Service.
Sorry I'm late.
I guess she got tuckered out from waiting.
I apologize.
I know it was an emergency, but I ended
up casting my family aside again.
What are you even saying, Twilight?
Your "family" is a part of the mission.
Wait, my mission was supposed to be the vacation...
So I guess I wasn't supposed to... uh...