Get behind me, you two!
I've never seen something like that before.
It seems best suited to mid-ranged combat.
I guess we won't be
able to just flee the scene.
In that case...
I can't get close to him.
He's really using that thing
to its full potential.
What's going on?
A fight?
I-Is he going to hurt her?
Th-This isn't good.
Someone should get security.
We couldn't be more conspicuous if we tried!
What should I do?
The last thing we need is for this to escalate!
Wow, this is amazing!
I-Is that Anya?!
She's the last person I wanted to see here!
Wow! The lady from the circus is so cool!
Oh, it's just a street performance!
This really is a luxury cruise!
Sh-She really saved me!
It seems like Anya didn't recognize me, either.
Now's my chance.
Amazing!
There's nothing I can use as cover.
We're at the center of attention,
and everyone needs to come out unscathed.
To top it off, I can't even get close to him!
Something isn't right.
It's like my legs aren't listening to me.
What's going on?
Am I afraid of getting hurt?
I don't even have to worry about a
severe injury with a weapon like that.
You've got this, lady!
Hurry and beat that guy up
before Daddy comes out!
I'll just have to risk getting hit,
grab his chain, and pull him down...
No, I think I need to make
this look more showy,
or they'll become suspicious.
What do I do, what do I do...
You gotta one-up her
with some chain tricks, man!
Tch. I messed up, and now there
are tons of people watching us.
What a pain.
I guess I'll just have to kill everyone else, too.
Bravo!
Man, that was amazing!
Not too clear on what
the premise was, though.
Mommy is terrifying.
I think I'll start listening to
her a little more from now on.
Finally, the perfect outfit!
This should make her happy.
Oh, that's right!
I need to get back to the shop!
Where did you go, little girl?
There was a circus over there.
Anya wins yet again.
I was able to help Mommy
and complete the mission
without Daddy finding out.
This was the most exciting
and valiant adventure yet!
I'd like all of these items.
Y-You look lovely, sir.
This is perfect.
No matter how you look at it,
I am clearly a fun and happy dad.
Could you be any lamer? Yikes.
Let's go.
Man, that had to have been the argument
to end all arguments.
And that ice pick? Talk about scary!
I'm surprised we haven't had to deal
with a murder case at this point.
That's what I'm saying!
Blue Lace No. 89 and
Mermaid eau de toilette...
Her perfume is different compared to
the ones I noticed at her mansion.
A new fragrance for a new face, I guess.
There were at least two women and one man.
Perhaps the person I can't smell
is that elusive bodyguard.
It's me. Where are they headed?
I don't know.
There's a very high chance they've snuck
into one of the lower-class cabins,
but I haven't heard anything yet.
I guess I'll plant someone there.
Considering the ship's route,
they're probably going to make their move
tomorrow night at the earliest.
When that time comes, they'll have
no choice but to show themselves.
Keep up the good work.
Yeah.
Did you find them?
No, not yet.
We've been ordered to go
to the third deck for now.
Man, talk about a useless informant.
He better not be thinking he can just
make off with our money.
Ain't no way we'd let that happen.
In fact, I might just pay him a visit
and get a refund before we leave.
What are you gonna do once we get paid?
Let's see. First, I'm gonna get some chicks...
I guess idiots can seep their way into anything.
I may as well make some preparations.
Hey, where are you going?
Our room's this way.
Mommy's in trouble...
Yor is?
I mean, I'm sure she's working late,
but that doesn't concern you.
It's past your bedtime. Let's head back.
But Anya's adventure has only just begun.
She never contacted us,
so she's probably busy.
No one followed us, and no wiretaps.
Looks like we've finally got a moment to relax.
It looks like the director
has prepared some food for us, as well.
We have everything we need to survive
until the other boat arrives.
There, there. You'll be fine, my love.
I almost pissed my pants!
What the hell is with those guys?!
Who in their right mind does that?
These guys were trying
to murder us in broad daylight!
You can't be serious! I wanna go home!
Could you quit making an ass of yourself?
But did you see how built those guys were?!
They're inhuman!
Honestly, you're just
a complete coward, aren't you?
It's so pathetic I could almost cry.
The little guy, too?
Make sure you don't grow up to be like him, okay?
By the way, why'd you come with me?
You had no reason to put yourself
in all this danger.
You could've just stayed
in the new organization.
W-Well... that's because you're... uh...
What?
Y-Y'know...
P-Please have some faith in me.
I'm not so rotten that I'd forget
everything the boss did for me.
After the war ended,
food became extremely scarce.
If the family weren't running that black market,
I would've starved to death.
Here, you can have this.
Shh. This'll be our little secret.
Hey, Olka. Where'd you go?
To this day, I remember exactly
how that bread tasted.
That's all the reason I need to stay here.
Zeb...
P-Plus, the alternative isn't much better!
Hapoon's being all buddy-buddy with pro-war
extremists to get rich through arms dealing!
He's a total piece of shit!
Leave this to me!
Even if Hapoon's lackeys come
after us, I'll beat 'em all to a pulp.
I'm sorry! I take it back!
Good work, sir.
Earlier, you forgot about our secret knock
and went to answer the door, didn't you?
I'm sorry. I'll be more careful.
I'd like the three of you
to rest up for tomorrow.
I'll leave Forger on guard at the door.
Wh-Who could sleep in these circumstances?!
What will you do, sir?
I'm going to patrol the cabin.
I'll eliminate any assassin
I come across, one by one.
Now, this is just hysterical.
You're real calm for someone
whose life is on the line.
You're not right in the head.
We're simply doing our job.
So is "kill or be killed"
something that comes naturally to you?
It's been over ten years since the war ended,
but I guess we just can't
help ourselves from fighting each other.
Conflict is just another part of human nature.
Whether it's wartime or peacetime...
We are nothing more than
soldiers for our countries.
If necessary, I will signal with my footsteps.
Keep your guard up.
Yes, sir.
Forger...
Y-Yes?
Don't drop your guard.
The smallest mistake will get us killed.
That was intense... Are they all like that?
The director is right.
You three should get some rest.
Even if all you do is lay down.
I need you at peak capacity for tomorrow.
Please remain clothed so we
can move at a moment's notice.
G-Got it...
I'm turning off the lights.
Come to think of it...
I was never able to contact Loid or Anya.
Though, I couldn't in these circumstances anyway.
What if the sluggishness I was feeling...
was the fear of them seeing me get hurt?
If they ever had to see me
so terribly wounded like that,
I don't think I could look them in the eyes anymore.
Aren't they just an alibi for the work you do?
That's right, Yor.
I need to get my priorities straight.
Why am I doing this?
What am I doing this for?
Man... Why do I gotta walk the dog
so early in the morning?
Borf! Borf!
You shut your mouth, mutt!
I don't want anything to do with you or the kid!
I should be saving a country,
not walking your ass!
Oh, what a cute doggie!
Huh?
Good morning.
I haven't seen you before.
Do you live around here?
Uh, yeah...
Hope I see you again sometime!
You wanna come live with me?
I am Twilight, the best spy Westalis has to offer.
No matter the situation,
even in the face of death,
I've always been able to keep my cool.
My attention to detail,
split-second decisions, and adaptability...
All skills I have carefully mastered.
That's how it's always been.
But...
Stay away from me!
Could you be any lamer?
I'd gotten ahead of myself.
There's still a lot I don't know about.
I can't only rely on information
and my experiences.
The root of everyone's fear is the unknown.
Death, invisible spirits,
neighbors and nearby countries...
Not knowing who or what they are brings fear.
Some just accept that
they'll never understand these things.
Some will act like they don't see them.
Others find peace of mind in making assumptions
based on their own beliefs.
I... am a secret agent.
I do not fear the unknown.
No, I acknowledge my fear,
then deal with it accordingly.
Just as scientists shone
light into the darkness...
Just as they discovered
viruses and vaccines...
On the second day of this cruise,
I will overcome the obstacles before me.
What?
They called it off?
I was told they had an awful fight last night.
The missus was quite displeased when she
found Mr. Grey had pooped his pants,
so she's not in the mood to be social.
I-I see...
What about the meet and greet?
It's probably back to square one.
Don't worry about it. You two
didn't do anything wrong.
I will take care of the family.
You two are free to do
whatever you'd like today.
Y-Yes, sir.
Hell yeah!
Adventure! Exploring!
Another day, another adventure to be had!
My observational skills,
split-second decisions, and adaptability...
Super-exciting adventures!
Super-exciting journey...
I fell asleep yesterday, but I gotta find a way
to help Mommy, and fast!
But...
Daddy! Mommy's in trouble!
We gotta save her, and fast!
What?! What are you talking about?!
Impossible! Yor goes around having battles?!
I can't believe this! Oh my God!
There's gotta be another way!
I have to figure out a place to lose Daddy.
Daddy, look! They have a golf course!
Did you want to play?
I don't know why, but grown-ups love golf.
My plan is to sneak away while
Dad is concentrating on golf.
H-He got a hole-in-one on every hole!
Bravo!
Shock! He already finished!
Why don't you give it a try?
It's fun.
Grr! Hngh!
Calm down. Eyes on the ball.
It's about time for lunch.
I'm not leaving 'till I get it in!
Hmm... Having her experience
success is important.
I guess I'll let her keep
playing until she gets it in.
Decide. Adapt.
Stop yelling. You'll bother the other guests.
Grr!
I fell for Daddy's trap and
ended up wasting time!
I need to figure out a plan B!
Enjoying your food?
Information is Daddy's favoritest thing.
There's no way I won't lose him in here!
I've read all these books before.
Well, as long as she's having fun...
Shoot!
Puzzles are so much fun!
I wonder if Daddy wants
to help me with this humongous puzzle.
If I just need to line up the pieces,
I can finish in two minutes.
Let's see...
Observe.
I wasn't able to escape Daddy,
and now it's time for dinner!
Heck, at some point, I forgot about Mommy
and was just enjoying myself!
Why?!
What's with the death stare?!
You were clearly having fun!
Why do you look so grumpy now?!
Did I make a mistake somewhere?!
Calm down, Twilight. Face the unknown!
Does she hate me?
Is this her rebellious phase?!
At this rate, the Forgers
are going to fall apart.
D-Do you have a stomachache?
Are you all right?
A-Am I making him worry?
I'm fine.
I'm really enjoying my adventure.
I see. Well, that's good.
But Mommy's gone, so I feel a bit sad.
I like it the most when we all spend time together.
So it's up to me to help Mommy finish her mission!
I see.
Yeah...
It would've been nice if Yor
could've had some time off.
She's still a very small child.
If you'd like, we can ask her if she
has time to meet tomorrow.
Do you know where Mommy is?
No, but I'll leave a message
with the concierge.
Once we get a reply,
let's meet up with her.
All right!
I know. There are going to be
fireworks up on the deck later.
It's the main event for tonight,
so maybe they'll be on the deck, too.
There'll be a big crowd, so I don't know
if we'll find her, but do you want to go?
Fireworks! I wanna go!
Yes.
That was the director.
He's received word from the rendezvous ship.
They said they're ready.
The meetup is in 4 hours,
but we need to get ready now.
And most importantly, the enemy's closing in on this deck.
We need to leave this room
and go somewhere else.
Everyone, please change.
Make use of one of these wigs.
A-All right.
It's me. Any movement?
I've intercepted an anonymous secret message.
It's different from the State
Security Service's frequency.
It could be a signal to the target.
Could be.
All right. Attention, everyone.
Stand by at stage three positions
and ambush them.
All right. No enemies in the area.
Let's go.