A resort!
And I stick the landing.
Stop jumping around. You'll fall over.
I'm glad all these State Security
officers are keeping an eye out for the bomber,
but I can't help but feel
their gaze. It's incredibly distracting.
You know, Daddy...
I've heard that at times like this,
normal dads would be joyously frolicking
with their daughters.
Let's enjoy this resort to the fullest!
So predictable.
Mommy!
Yor...
You got our message?
Yes.
I was given the day off today.
Your face seems a little swollen.
Huh?
He figured it out.
Are you all right?
Oh, um...
I had to intervene when our clients
got into an argument,
and unfortunately...
I see.
So you weren't able to get their business?
Yeah, it fell through.
But we did everything we could.
And in the end, they were pleased with the trip.
That's good enough for me.
I see.
Are we gonna play today?
Yes! We're gonna make up for lost time!
Let's enjoy!
It's enjoyin' time!
These guys look like Bond!
It's nice how peaceful this place is.
Indeed.
Though, the cruise ride to get here
was rather unnerving.
I wish we could live in a world as peaceful as this.
And I'll do anything to make that happen.
Daddy! Mommy!
I wanna do the thing where you go into
the ocean and look at fishies!
Huh? Is this something I'd need a swimsuit for?
I can't. I don't know how to talk
my way around the wound in my chest.
Actually, we might get eaten
by sharks, so never mind.
Huh?! But...
Oh, I might be able to cover
it with this swimsuit.
Come on, Anya! Let's give it a go.
Don't worry. There are no sharks.
Even if there are, I'd secretly beat them up.
Ba bwishies bar bo bretty!
Bes. Bey book bo beliblous!
Now I wanna go surfing!
Let's do it!
Here comes a great wave, Anya!
Okee!
I'll give you a little push.
There!
Oh, no! I just finished a job,
so my sense of strength is still off!
Ooh!
Are you all right, Anya?!
I wanna do that again!
So thrilling!
Don't.
I'm so sorry! I'm so sorry!
I had lots of fun today!
Well, I'm glad.
We should probably head back to the ship soon.
You're right.
Oh...
All that fighting is starting to catch up with me...
Um... Yor?
Daddy... I'm getting sleepy, too.
I'm goin' to sleep.
Huh?!
Anya's one thing, but Yor, too?
I'm guessing this job was
pretty rough on her.
And yet, she gave Anya an enjoyable day out.
You did a great job.
This incident on the Lorelei...
It hasn't been announced publicly,
but a lot of passengers
have apparently gone missing.
All of them had forged IDs.
I did indeed see a number of
suspicious-looking characters.
If any are involved in instigating
conflict between the East and West,
we should look into them.
Apparently the State Security Service thinks
there's another country involved in this.
I doubt they're going to let this incident
see the light of day, though.
We'll just keep our eye out for any
extremists in Ostania on our end.
This would involve Strix, as well.
I'm counting on you.
Understood.
So?
Putting aside the bombing incident,
how was your vacation?
Was little Anya happy?
I've had enough vacations.
They're far more backbreaking than my usual missions.
I can never tell if it's skill or pure luck
that he's survived this long.
Good morning.
Oh, Yor. Already back from your trip?
Y'know, Yor, I still haven't forgiven you for going.
Now, did ya get a souvenir for me?
Again, it was a business trip.
Yes. I got this lovely
souvenir from the gift shop!
What do you think?
What is this thing?
It's a skeleton keychain.
Oof, this is the worst.
Not really what I had in mind...
What made you think this was a good idea?
Usually, people would get
their coworkers wine,
snacks, or other consumables for souvenirs.
O-Oh, I see!
Daddy wouldn't buy this for me.
Please, Mommy?
I clearly said I'd buy that for her, didn't I?
This is really cool, Anya!
This'd be a good souvenir for my coworkers!
What should I do?
Loid picked out some snacks for Yuri's gift.
Should I just give them those?
But there won't even be enough for everyone...
Well, I can't say I didn't expect this from you.
What? Wine would've been so much better than this.
I guess I'll give it to my kid.
Skip, skip, la, la, la!
You seem to be a good mood, Yuri.
Did something happen with your sister?
I'm surprised you knew
this was about my sister!
Are you some kind of psychic?
Maybe.
My sister's back from her business trip!
I'm going to stop by her place after work!
It's been so, so, so long since I've seen you!
But if she's back, that also means...
He's back.
That should do it.
It's quite a pain to prepare all this
every time her brother comes over.
But despite him being a relative,
he's a State Security Officer,
our biggest conflict of interest.
Letting my guard down even
a little may cost me dearly.
It'll probably look more convincing if
I move the pillows closer together.
I should also add more recent family photos.
Maybe I should prepare matching
pajamas, too, just in case.
Did you go anywhere during the break?
I went to see Pecasso's works
at the art museum!
I went to the National Opera
House and saw an orchestra.
Cool!
Good day, Anya!
Heh. Morning, please.
Oh? You look a little tanned.
Did you go somewhere?
Heh. I suppose I could let you in on it.
It's a long story, but it's true.
I spent my vacation sailing the seas.
It was the start of an epic adventure.
Who is she trying to be here?
I've now been aboard...
a luxury cruise ship!
Wait, what did you say?!
What?!
Wow, Anya, you must be super influential!
Wait, are you serious?! You got to ride that ship?!
Maybe you should stop looking down on her, Damian.
I was wrong, Anya!
You Forgers are more than worthy of
visiting my place!
Come over!
I do what I have to
for the sake of the mission.
Aw, that's pretty normal.
Shock!
It's not normal at all! It was super huge!
It was called Prindess Lalalai, or something!
You mean the Princess Lorelei?
I rode on it there before I enrolled here.
It was okay, I guess.
Shock!
We stayed in the imperial suite, but the
furnishings didn't quite do it for me.
Shock!
I stayed in a third class jail cell...
Pfft!
If I had to stay in third class,
I wouldn't dream of bringing it up!
Hey, quit it. Don't make fun of the commoners.
Just the other day, I got to
fly over Münk in a helicopter.
It was so much fun!
We stayed at a first class hotel in Bayan,
and I ate tons of yummy things!
Hmph. So what?
I got my dad to let me have a party with
the actress from Berlint in Love, Rachel.
About a hundred people
got to hear behind-the-scenes stories
and partake in a gift exchange.
It was just so much fun!
That's amazing, Becky!
The Blackbells sure are amazing!
You're on another level!
Hey, tell us more about Rachel!
Is she just as pretty in person?
You gotta introduce me to her!
Yeah, well, on my ship...
There were, like, a hundred
really insane people!
What do you mean by that?
Were there, like, celebrities onboard?
Oh, like who?
Lots of people from lots of different countries!
Huh...
Wait, so foreign celebrities?
Wow!
Well, don't keep us waiting! Tell us who!
You know...
Like Sickle-and-Chain Barnaby.
Who?!
Who the heck's that? Never heard of them.
A street performer?
Well, who else was there?
Huh?
Um...
There was Thwomp-man,
who commanded elephants...
And Shwoop-man, who could teleport.
Who even are these people? A circus?
Um... Bad guys.
Bad guys? Really?
What? Did you run into some pirates?
That must've sucked!
I didn't hear anything like that on the news.
Don't take her seriously.
That's right!
The thing with the bad guys
will never see the light of day!
I can't believe I got my hopes up.
Tsk, tsk, tsk.
They weren't on the news.
That's because they're a
bunch of secret bad guys
that even the government doesn't know about!
The truth is they came from the
bottom of the ocean...
They were octopeople!
I heroically defeated
them one by one with the stabby thing!
Actually, Mommy did.
So, what did you and Rachel talk about?
I wanna meet her too!
Shock!
And so... the peace of the
world... was protec...
No way! Samantha was there, too?!
Aw, I wish I got to meet them.
Wow, she sure is something.
She's such a grandiose liar.
I guess in one way, she's a hero.
At least you never get bored watching her.
What the heck is an octoperson
who commands elephants?
Right?
All right, everyone. Get to your seats.
Did you all enjoy your break?
Sir, apparently Forger
defeated some octopeople.
Wow, that's amazing.
I totally understand.
It's human nature to want to puff
yourself up sometimes.
And if that helps you become who you want to be,
there's nothing wrong with that.
That's what my mom told me.
Becky!
But you should be careful about lying
or you'll end up a loner like me.
It's been so long since I've seen you!
I missed you so much!
Here you go. I bought you some snacks.
Wow! I'll treasure this forever!
Note that these have an expiry date, though.
Then I'll frame a photo
and admire it every single day!
Must he be so loud?
Borf!
I'm back from school.
Welcome home!
Oh? What's the matter, Anya?
Borboborf?
You tried acting like a big shot
and got made fun of?
They called me a liar.
I cried a little.
Why would you lie like that?
For Plan B!
How do you know about that?!
I just wanted attention.
Casually telling lies whenever
the impulse strikes is a dangerous habit.
Deception must be pursued strategically,
and you must commit to it completely.
Stake your life on it!
First, you need to gather enough
details to make your lie convincing,
and work in some truth here and there.
But be extravagantly...
I see. Right... yeah.
Don't tell lies.
I've seen so many of them
throughout my life.
Those who lie are nothing but trash.
They're nothing but filth
who pollute our country.
Me? The only reason I'm lying
about who I am is for my sister!
Everything I do for my sister is righteous!
Yeah. Those who lie are trash.
R-Right...
Of course, you should be comfortable
just the way you are!
People will get along with you
if you're just honest!
Lying is too much work,
so I'll try not to do it anymore.