We've been waiting for you, Briar Rose.
Hello.
Your garden is as lovely as ever, Shopkeeper.
It is, isn't it?
With proper watering, pruning,
and consistent care,
we can ensure that the world
remains a beautiful place.
Welcome, Briar Rose.
The heather smells so nice.
The leaves of the spindle tree
also look lovely right now.
Take a look.
Wow!
Goodness, that startled me!
Pardon me.
I was worried that the family life
might've dulled your instincts,
but they seem as honed as ever.
Now I can let you serve our
next customer without worry.
Of course! I am ready to end
any evildoer at any time!
How reassuring. However...
This time, you'll be protecting the client.
Protecting?
Have you heard of the Gretcher family?
For generations, they've been a powerful force
in maintaining this country's underworld.
A little while back, the boss and his two sons
were killed in an internal dispute.
The only Gretchers to survive the incident
were Olka Gretcher and her son.
She's being kept in a safehouse for the time being.
But the man who took over their
organization, Leonardo Hapoon,
is desperately trying to find her.
He's put a bounty on her,
so now she's the target of every hitman
in the country.
We've decided that having her seek asylum
in another country is her best option.
She'll escape by sea.
To make sure she isn't caught by the coastal guard,
she'll take a regular passenger cruise
and rendezvous with our allies.
I'd like you to stay by her side
until she's handed over.
Protecting a high-level mafia member
from an army of trained hitmen?
In an ideal world,
the odds wouldn't be so stacked against her,
but we just want to play it safe.
The Gretcher family boss was a man
I owe a debt of gratitude to.
I'd greatly appreciate if you took this on.
I see...
Well, what about my job at city hall?
Also, if I'm going to be gone for a couple of days,
I have to think of an excuse to give my family.
You needn't worry about that.
I've devised a plan that allows you to do this
under the guise of your civil servant work.
Your manager will fill you in
on the details later.
I knew I could count on you, Briar Rose.
Continue the fight to keep the world
a beautiful place.
A-All right. I'll give it my best!
This'll be one of my biggest jobs in a while.
I must be prepared.
Yuri!
Yor?!
I haven't seen you take this train before!
Uh, yeah... I just got back
from a business trip.
Actually, I was arresting
a political dissident.
Well, good work.
Would you like to join us for dinner?
Can I?!
Actually, I don't think I should.
Loidy's at your place,
and I've still got some work to do.
Like sorting through transcripts.
Goodness, are you ever going to get along with him?
I won't.
Have you been eating properly?
Make sure you're not leaving
your socks lying around.
Yor, I'm not a kid anymore.
Yes...
Yes, of course.
Now stopping at Fogue Square.
I can't keep clinging to you forever.
Fogue Square.
Though I just did the other day...
It's you who should start relying
on me if anything ever happens.
I'd happily put an end to Loidy!
See you later.
Yor!
I guess Yuri's all grown up now.
Of course he is.
He has a proper job,
and he's making a living on his own.
He doesn't need my help anymore.
Is there any real reason
I need to continue my job as a killer?
Too bad! Yer seventh-place prize, one brush.
Damn it!
Come on up fer a chance to win big
at our biannual grand raffle!
Fer just 30 dalc, ya get a chance
at winnin' one of these amazin' prizes!
First prize, believe it or not,
is two tickets fer that luxury cruise
everyone's buzzin' about lately!
Keep those tickets comin'!
Daddy.
I'm gonna get on that boat
and have a big adventure.
I see. How valiant of you.
Now gimme that raffle ticket.
Just remember, we only have one.
That sucks!
Here's yer sixth-place premium brush.
What the hell, man?
Is there even a winning ticket in there?
First place is still up for grabs, y'all!
Ya bunch of fools.
Yer all dropping money on
a prize yer not gonna win.
That cruise is as good as mine.
I've made sure of it.
Yeah, yeah, I know.
I just have to pretend we're strangers.
The first-place ticket is stuck
to the top of the box.
None of ya are gettin' it!
Call it an employee benefit!
Feelin' excited, Cindy?
I don't even like cruises,
but a free trip's a free trip I guess.
Aw, too bad! Here's your
fifth-place gold brush!
Oh? Are you gonna be our lucky little lady?
Here you go. Hope you win!
Go on and get yer losin' ticket, pipsqueak.
First place is goin'
to that nice lady behind ya.
Wha—
We have a winner!
How the hell?!
I'm home, Loid and Anya!
Look at this, Mommy!
I won a fancy boat trip!
What?!
She managed to win first prize
at a department store's raffle.
My, that's amazing!
Too amazing. It's making me
wonder if it's some sort of trap.
Daddy is suspicious of everything.
Since there are two tickets,
why don't you go with her, Yor?
I still have to work.
I'm so excited! I've never been to the ocean!
Borf, borf!
You have to stay home, Bond.
Borf!
A trip on the Princess Lorelei?
This is the same ship
I'm going to be on for my work trip!
Huh?
And it's the exact ship
that's leaving on Friday...
You're going on a work trip?
Oh, yes.
Um... the city is trying to attract
a famous grocery chain,
and I'm supposed to be entertaining a VIP.
Ah, must be a modern form of urban planning.
It's actually a job to protect
a very important client from assassins.
A job battling assassins?!
If they end up on the same ship as me,
it'll add another layer of complexity
to the mission.
What should I do?
We can't cause trouble for Mommy.
Forget about this ooting.
Who cares?
I wanna relax on a big fancy boat.
You're thinking the exact same thing.
You're right.
If we go and help Mommy with her work,
we could kill two birds with one stone.
Be honest with yourself.
You know you just want to go see the ocean.
Let me go on the boat! The big one!
Or I'm gonna go crazy!
Oh, dear...
Well, I guess I'll ask my boss
if I can get some paid time off.
Sure, that's fine.
Huh?!
I'll pull some strings so you can
get time off at the hospital, too.
Uh... Thank you very much.
Are you kidding me?
I'm going to work you down to the bone!
HQ may or may not be trying to cut
back on our shady overtime practices.
I see...
Well, little Anya's care and education
are part of Strix, as well.
Agent Twilight,
I order you to execute a vacation
as skillfully as any other mission.
An ooting! An ooting!
It's been so long since I've had
an ooting with Mom and Dad!
It has been a while,
though I'm supposed to be on the job.
You'll fall out.
If not for this bodyguard job,
the three of us could've enjoyed
this vacation together.
What in the world am I saying?!
I need to get my priorities straight!
What's the matter, Mom?
Oh, we'll be getting off at the next stop!
But maybe...
Just maybe...
if this could be my last job...
It's huge!
Excited, excited, excited, excited,
excited, excited, excited, excited!
Calm down.
Well, I have to meet up with my coworkers,
so I'll see you later.
I'll contact you when I get the chance.
Sorry that you won't be able to join us.
You've got this, Mom!
A pool!
A circus!
A game room!
And...
The ocean!
Dad, this ship is so cool!
This feels like the start of a big adventure!
Well, this luxurious cruise ship
is Ostania's pride and joy.
Let's hurry and go exploring!
After we put our luggage in our room.
Our own suite! So exciting!
It appears we've accidentally come
to the jail. This is the wrong place.
This is the place.
This is what you're gonna
get down in third class.
Please look forward to my grand
adventure in our next feature.
You won this cruise in a raffle.
Don't get greedy now.
But this'll be my first bunkbed!
I call the top bunk!
Do as you please. Just don't fall off.
Yor and her company are probably
in the first-class rooms.
Why does she get the good rooms?
Well, she's here to do business, so...
Allow us to formally introduce ourselves.
I am Matthew McMahon,
director of policy at Berlint City Hall.
This is Heymann and Vides
from our business development team.
And this is Forger.
I'm Furseal Grey, from the store development
group at Arhaus Department Stores.
This is my wife, Shaty.
I'm sorry about the kid.
Please! We want you and your family
to enjoy your time here!
If your wife needs any assistance whatsoever,
allow Forger to take care of it.
Thank you.
So this is Ms. Olka from the Gretcher family.
She looks completely
different from her picture.
I guess she had to change her appearance
to help her escape.
It's a pleasure to meet you.
Pleasure.
So this is Ms. Olka's bodyguard?
Is she really capable enough for this job?
This Princess Lorelei
cruise will be a short one.
Three days and two nights,
just visiting the nearby islands.
We hope you'll be able to relax
and enjoy this trip, Mr. Grey.
Though it's no department store,
this ship does have a shopping mall.
Would you like to go take a look?
These two are just normal employees
who don't know the truth, right?
Sure, let's go.
I'm fine. I'll stay here with the baby.
I see. Well,
I'll have Forger stay behind to tend to your needs.
Right this way, Mr. Grey.
Huh? Um...
Is one bodyguard going to be enough?
Shouldn't we all stay together?
She should be quite safe in her room.
We will first be checking
the rest of the ship.
You needn't worry. She is quite strong.
Your mission is to protect the sole survivors
of the tragedy: Olka and her son.
We've received intel that the one pursuing her
has several assassins on his side.
You are authorized to eliminate threats
by any means.
I'm counting on you, Briar Rose.
They checked for signs of infiltration
and escape routes before we left,
but I can't relax
until I check everything myself.
Though, I'm sure the manager has also checked.
Huh, I guess you really are one of them.
Huh? Uh, yes.
One of who?
Um, you are Olka, right?
I am. Though, I'd prefer
if you didn't use that name while we're here.
Oh! I'm so sorry!
Oh, did you wake up?
Oh, I'm so terribly sorry!
Mama... Mama...
It's so strange.
I look completely different,
but he still knows that I'm his mother.
Maybe it's because of my voice, my scent,
or that his eyesight hasn't fully developed yet.
I'm a little sad that I'll never hear
about how much we look alike,
but I guess I have bigger things to care about.
Besides, he looks like his father,
so it'd turn out the same either way.
Y-Your husband?
He seemed like a lovely person.
The man you just saw
is a member of our organization.
He's just playing the part.
He is a good man, though.
My husband was killed along
with the rest of my family.
My son is all I have left now.
I'm so sorry, I...
It's fine. I guess it's just what happens
when you choose a life of crime.
But I've grown tired of that.
I don't need power or money.
I just want to live a quiet, peaceful life.
There, there. What's got you so spooked?
Excuse me, miss.
Can I be a bit selfish?
Ever since my family was killed,
I've been forced to live in hiding.
I'd like to spread my wings just a little bit.
I also want to give him a breath of fresh air.
But we should really confer with the director first...
Please. Just for a little bit.
The ones after me don't know what I look like,
nor should they know that I'm on this ship.
And besides, I'll have you
to protect me, won't I?
V-Very well.
Just for a little bit.
If you keep acting that suspicious,
won't you bring more attention to us?
Well, I'm looking out for the enemy, but...
Your family is on this ship?
Yes, my husband and daughter.
Daddy! We need to hurry up and
explore the ship before it sinks!
It's not going to sink!
Stop scaring everyone!
But...
This ship certainly is huge.
There seems to be quite a few celebrities present.
Just in case of a terrorist incident,
I should check for any suspicious people
aboard and confirm the layout of the ship.
I need to figure out who's meeting who,
as well as where and when...
What are you doing, Daddy?
Shit, I slipped into my usual habits!
I order you to execute a vacation
as skillfully as any other mission!
I must rest.
I must try my hardest to enjoy my vacation
to the fullest!
Why don't we go see a show?!
You're always so serious.
Ah...
But why would you bring them with you?
Oh, I didn't. It was all a complete coincidence.
My family doesn't know about my real job.
So if a fight does happen to break out,
it would be very inconvenient
if they were to spot me.
Actually, even having
any of the other guests see me...
Well, if they're in third class,
you probably won't see them
unless we go to a common area.
There's nothing to worry about.
Sure, but...
You seem really worried about this.
Aren't they just an alibi for the work you do?
Yes, that's right...
I guess that's what they are.
Oh, of course! Let's go outside already!
Oh, wait.
I'll let you borrow this.
It feels so nice.
Um, this outfit...
Now we're just two moms enjoying the breeze.
It's better than the suit.
And if your husband sees you, he probably
won't recognize you unless he's up close.
I guess you have a point.
Ah...
What a nice, peaceful breeze.
Wow, the shore is completely gone!
You're right.
There's so much I left behind.
Oh, dear. Are you getting cold?
I guess we can head back.
Um, Shaty!
I-I'm going to give this my best!
I'll make sure to protect...
I promise to properly do my job!
Besh! Besh!
Yes, I will do my very besht!
Gram.
Huh?
That's his name. Just like my father's. His real name.
Dam!
It's a pleasure to meet you, Gram!
Want to hold him as we walk back?
May I?!
I need to make sure I don't break any of his bones!
I'm so sorry! I'll give him back to you, Shaty!
Hey, there's a show at five!
Let's grab drinks at the bar upstairs.
Wow! You can even go shopping here!
Dad!
What's the matter? Don't stray.
I'm certain you will win the next election.
No, no, those stocks right now are—
Well, this isn't good. The lock to
the emergency passage is broken.
I was almost forced to stay behind.
This is so good!
This company's products—
So there you have it.
E-226, all clear.
What am I going to do with them?
Gram.
That's—name. Just like—father's.
It's a—to meet you, Gram!
I'm so sorry! I'll give him back to you, Shaty!
Shaty, Shaty...
Shaty Hutton, room 2125.
Shaty Copeland, room 3064.
Shaty Grey, room 8053.