I can't believe her!
Why does she get to go on
an all-expenses-paid vacation?
It's supposed to be a wine and dine
with clients, not a vacation.
Well, I could've done that, too!
Apparently, one of the guests had a baby,
so whoever went had to have a kid.
They're apparently both from the same town, too.
That's what the guy from HR told me.
This isn't fair!
Imagine the kinds of food she gets to eat!
I'm so jealous I could die!
I'm plenty happy with hot dogs
and the cheap beer we get after work.
Totally.
Isn't the food here great?
It's prepared by chefs who work
at a five-star hotel based in Berlint.
Also, the ship's state-of-the-art engineering
and stunning interior design
were both funded by the city!
It's bad to talk at your client, you two.
Well, I'd love to eat at that hotel someday.
This is delicious.
I'm so nervous, I can't taste a thing.
Calm down.
They aren't going to attack
in such a crowded space.
And third-class passengers, such as your family,
can't enter this restaurant.
So please, act your part.
Y-Yes, sir.
Would you like to grab a couple
drinks downstairs, Mr. Grey?
S-Sure.
I'm going to head back to the room.
Be cautious of anyone following
you on the way back to the room.
Understood.
There are no signs that anyone came in here.
We're safe.
I guess we were all anxious for nothing.
W-We can't let our guard down, though!
There's no guarantee that the ship
is completely safe.
We have thirty hours before we
rendezvous with the other ship.
If I were the enemy,
I'd strike right before you move over.
I wouldn't want to cause a commotion here,
where there's no way to escape.
Even if intel hasn't been leaked,
there's always a chance
the enemy could figure us out.
It's quite plausible
that they'll attack tomorrow.
At least, that's what the director said.
Let's keep our guard up!
Yeah, I guess you're right.
Maybe I just want to relax
and believe I'm in the clear.
But this isn't just my problem anymore.
I need to get a grip.
Right.
Once we reach our destination
and confirm that it's safe,
make sure you let him play to his hearts content.
You don't seem like someone
who would work in the underworld.
Huh? Oh, I'm terribly sorry! I'll try harder.
If we're able to escape safely,
what are all of you going to do afterward?
If there's no longer a threat,
we'll await further orders.
We've told the two city hall workers
that the Greys would like to be
by themselves on the third day,
so that won't be a problem.
The director will smooth things over
when you leave, as well.
What about you? Aren't you going to see your family?
Huh? I mean, this is supposed to be a work trip...
I did say that I would contact
them when I had a moment, but...
This ship is stopping at an island
resort on the third day, isn't it?
I hope you and your family are able
to enjoy some quality time together.
No, I, uh...
Don't overeat just because it's a buffet.
I played lots. Now I'm starving.
What happened to your table manners?
It's been a while since
we've had dinner without Mama.
Yeah, it's quieter than usual.
You're being sappy.
I-I am not! I was just responding to what you said!
Just eat so we can go back to the room.
These cashews are exquisite.
Feelin' tipsy yet, Mr. Grey?
I could never in these circumstances.
We have got to play darts more often!
You did great, Mr. Grey.
Sorry, I forgot something.
You're such an airhead, Director!
We'll meet ya up ahead!
That game of darts was just the beginning!
How about another drink, Mr. Grey?
You know you wanna...
Thanks, but I'm gonna head back now.
Tch.
Answer my questions with a yes or a no.
Are you an assassin hired
by Leonardo Hapoon?
You only get two seconds to answer.
Next, I'll break your leg.
Are you one of Hapoon's assassins?
Are there any assassins
other than yourself?
How many in total?
Oh, sorry about that. That wasn't
a yes or no question, was it?
Tell me how many friends
you have and their locations.
Th-They aren't my friends.
I have no idea how many are on board.
We're all working on our own.
It's first come, first served.
Some guy is selling us intel.
That's how I knew to tail you guys.
Shaty Grey in room 8053...
Looks like I had the right person.
Oh, welcome back, Director.
What was that? You're about
to poop your pants, Mr. Grey?
That's an emergency!
Let's hurry back to your room!
You two, rest up for tomorrow.
D-Director?
Several assassins have snuck on board.
They know your aliases and room.
Our organization was carrying
out this plan in utmost secrecy.
There's no way our intel
could've been leaked.
Do you have any ideas? Make a slip-up, maybe?
No.
Did you?
No, I didn't, but...
Three days ago, I did make one phone call.
Just to my parents back home.
You fool!
I didn't say anything that would
jeopardize our plan. That's the truth!
I'm never gonna see them again,
so I needed to say goodbye!
That's all it was! I swear!
Tch. Save your breath.
We don't have time to track the enemies.
"First come, first served"?
I was naïve...
They were never going to wait until tomorrow!
We probably won't be going out again tonight,
so why don't we get more comfortable?
Good idea.
Director?
Oh, it's just room service.
But I didn't order anything.
You stole darts from the bar?
Please refrain from shooting
when there's a baby present!
Wow.
We'll carry him into the room.
Try not to leave a blood trail.
G-Got it.
You're saying we're surrounded
by potential enemies?
Some intel's been leaked, too.
We're abandoning this room.
There are a number
of vacant rooms in second class.
You need to take them there immediately.
What are you going to do?
I'll meet up with you
as soon as I finish up here.
U-Understood.
There's a chance the ship might
turn back if there's a commotion.
If you cannot hide the bodies,
avoid fighting to the best of your ability.
Just in case, hide your
face with this mask. Hurry!
Hello, this is guest services.
Oh, hello. This is room 8053.
I'm very sorry. The mister and missus
had a rather violent argument,
and they broke the door. Indeed.
We'd like to move to a different room.
I've lost contact with the Knocker.
Shaty from room 8053 is definitely our target.
The passenger list also names a husband.
If we include the woman I heard her talk to,
there'd be at least three of them.
That's not counting the baby.
Guess that's her muscle.
Looks like they're changing rooms.
Whatever room they move
to is probably a decoy.
And now they're on their guard
because someone had to jump the gun.
If their bodyguard is from Garden,
this isn't going to be easy.
Why don't we work together?
That means no infighting,
sharing information equally,
and we all split the reward.
Sounds like a pain in the ass.
Wouldn't it be faster to kill
any woman with a baby we see on board?
Don't lump assassins in with murderers.
Ours is a business based on trust.
Many of the family's regular patrons
are aboard this ship.
If you want to get paid,
try not to cause a commotion.
We'll also need you to keep reporting
to us without causing any leaks.
We're paying you good money.
I sell all of my information impartially.
You're competing with quite a few
trained assassins, so I wish you the best of luck.
Hey, aren't these masks just drawing
more attention to us?
Not at all.
There's a masquerade ball
taking place in the second class lounge.
Please do not remove them
under any circumstances.
Also, I need the two of you to listen
to what I say without turning around.
We are probably being followed.
Ever since we left the room.
So what are we going to do?!
Let's lose them before they
find out where we're going.
Th-This better work...
They're heading to the stern.
Their destination is probably
the second class lounge.
Okay, I'll make contact.
We're here!
Bloodlust!
They're attacking... in front of all these people?!
If I intercept and kill them,
it'll cause a commotion.
Then the rendezvous will get called off.
Something wrong?
Pardon me.
This needs to be done quietly.
Have I been spotted?
No, I should still be secure.
This'll be easy.
All I've gotta do is prick them
with this poison as I pass by.
I'll make sure it's quick—huh?!
I'm sorry sir, you've had one too many drinks.
And we're safe.
Huh? What is? Can I get my button back?
Wh-What?! What just happened to him?!
Sir?
Hey, Andre! They're entering the lounge!
Don't lose them! The black-haired
one is their bodyguard!
You can get the blonde from their blind spot!
Roger.
O-Oh, my.
Are you asking me to dance with you?
I'm terribly sorry. I'm not
very good at dancing.
And you know...
I may not look it, but I'm a married woman,
so I'll have to decline.
Have a wonderful night.
Andre, what happened?!
Please take a moment to rest.
Answer me, Andre!
It looks like we've lost them.
Let's get downstairs.
Once we're through the promenade,
we'll be in second class.
R-Right.
Daddy! I want this skeleton keychain!
Do you really want one?
I'm not sure why they even sell those here.
I want it! I want it! I want it! I want it! I want it!
Come on, it's time to head back to our room.
Oddly enough,
there seem to be wiretaps set
all over the place.
Countless members of the ruling
class and celebrities are aboard.
There must be plenty of State Security Officers
keeping an eye out.
Moreover, it seems there are other
groups I need to watch out for.
I'm going to lay low
and stay out of their crosshairs.
I want it! I want it! I want it now, dang it!
I want it! I want it! I want it! I want it! I want it!
So much for that.
He should just buy it for her.
Oh, she's adorable.
Wait, they had to have
overheard her entire tantrum!
Normally, a parent would
buy their child that.
You're suspicious. You must be a spy!
You piece of trash. You're under arrest!
What do I do?! Would a normal parent buy it?
Or would they refuse?
I mean, she clearly doesn't need this!
It feels inappropriate
to buy this for a child!
On the other hand, the wrong choice
could ultimately mean death...
I guess I don't need it after all.
I'll take them out.
"Don't cause a commotion?"
Hell if I care.
That broad and her brat
are worth 400,000 dalc.
I'm not gonna pretend I'm on your side
with this much on the line.
I'm Sickle-and-Chain Barnaby.
I never let my prey get away.
Sickle-and-Chain Barnaby?!
Who's that?
Here they come.
From what I heard, the black-haired one
is an experienced bodyguard.
I'll take her out first.
Mama!
That assassin is going to
try to battle Mama here.
Should I buy it or not?
I'm gonna sic this chained frog on you!
I hate frogs!
What's going on here?!
Y-Yor! You're an assassin who hates frogs?!
Let's get a divorce. The Forgers are done.
Let's get rid of Anya, too!
Eek!
Wh-What should I do?!
I was wrong, Anya.
How about I buy this for you
so we can call it a day?
It'll be a precious memory of our cruise.
I am a normal father. A good father.
Who cares about that stupid thing?!
Stay away from me!
What?!
Mama's gonna fight that guy any minute now!
I said I'd buy it for you, so cheer up, would you?
If he leaves the store, he's going to see them!
Eek! A battle!
What's going on here?!
What?! Yor, you go around having battles?!
If he even hears someone go,
"Eek!" it's the end!
I'm the one who said we should go on
this trip, so I have to do something...
Huh?! What does that expression even mean?
Is it sadness? Anger?!
What is going on in her head?!
Is she that hurt that I refused
to buy her this keychain?!
Are kids these days this emotionally unstable?!
No, that isn't it.
You should've known this, Twilight!
No matter how hard she tries to hide it...
Her heart was corrupted long ago!
She's been consumed by the forces of darkness!
Uh...
Well, little Anya's well-being
is part of Strix, as well.
The Handler must've foreseen all of this!
So that's what this vacation
has to do with world peace!
Failure is not an option.
Daddy's super wrong again.
Can I help you with anything?
Lately, this T-shirt and jacket
with the ship's logo are bestsellers.
This whale-print necktie
is popular among fathers.
Or maybe matching caps for you two?
We have a fitting room if you'd like
to try anything on!
No thanks, we'll pass for now.
I don't have time for that,
I need to check her mental state!
You just don't get it, do you Dad?
Huh?
Adventures are supposed
to be fun and exciting.
And when you have fun, you end up wanting to buy
fun little skeleton keychains,
or maybe a wooden sword.
But you're not having fun at all.
If you aren't having fun,
then I'm not having fun either.
I think I should be able to tell how excited
you are just by looking at you.
That's right.
I cannot believe that I,
the man with a thousand faces, had forgotten...
I must embody my role: A father and daughter
enjoying their vacation together!
Excuse me, I'd like to try those on.
In fact, I'll just wear them out.
Of course, sir.
I think the cute squiddy pants
would look good on you.
I'd like to try on all the clothes
you have in this establishment.
Oh, of course! Right this way.
I expect to see a very fun outfit from you.
Leave it to me.
Let me know if you need a
different size in anything!
Great, I'll keep him trapped
in there to buy time!
Now's my chance to help Mama!
Huh?!
Oh, no!
I forgot that he's the master of disguise!
He can change in an instant!
I don't get it!
No matter how you look at it,
these clothes don't match at all!
Is this going to work?
What does her idea of excitement look like?
Is there even a good answer to that?!
This isn't working!
I must become the man with a thousand outfits!
Huh? Aren't they going to battle?
Huh?
She actually evaded that?
And while protecting those two.
I didn't sense his bloodlust
up until the last second.
I need...
to take him seriously.