In an era where the nations of the world
are silently fighting a war of intelligence,
two countries were at odds with
each other: Ostania, in the east,
and Westalis, in the west.
In order to keep an eye on the actions of
a leading figure in Ostania's government
Westalis set Operation Strix in motion.
The one tasked with this operation
is the skilled agent, Twilight.
The mission given to the master of
disguise with a hundred faces was...
to start a family.
The father, Loid Forger, is a psychiatrist.
His true identity: a spy.
Code name: Twilight.
The mother, Yor Forger, is a civil
servant who works at city hall.
Her true identity: an assassin.
Code name: Briar Rose.
The daughter, Anya Forger.
Her true identity: a telepath
who can read people's minds.
The dog, Bond Forger.
His true identity: a canine seer
who can see the future.
As they maintain the facade
of an ordinary family life,
they're each fighting their own battles
behind closed doors.
Hello.
The customers have been served.
Oh, I'll be heading home immediately.
My husband asked me
to buy milk and eggs on my way home.
Shit, that's the infamous assassin, Briar Rose!
Yes. Thank you very much.
Die, you bitch!
This just in:
Several bodies believed to belong
to members of the Red Circus
have been found in a deserted building
in the Northern District.
The Red Circus, an extremist group
funded by foreign interests,
Daddy.
I wanna watch cartoons.
has committed numerous
indiscriminate acts of terrorism.
The news is boring.
No.
The authorities have concluded
that the incident was caused
There's so much information I can get
out of just a single news broadcast.
by internal strife within the group.
Next up, we have stock market news.
Okay, fine. You can change the channel.
In today's stock market,
we see a drastic decline
compared to the figures from last week.
Good day, Bondman.
Your mission today is to
tail a certain target.
You need to find out where they're
keeping their secret weapon
So cool.
and destroy it in order
to protect our country.
I'm home.
Welcome home, Yor—
Here—hngh—is the milk... and the eggs...
Uh, thanks a bunch, Yor.
Um, is something the matter?
Oh, I'm fine...
I'm just a little... well...
I can't tell him.
He can't know that while I was at work
I went to an extremist hideout,
killed all of them,
then got shot in the butt by a straggler!
I've been treated since then, but still...
Sh-She was shot with a gun?!
Are you going to die, Mommy?
Don't worry, Anya.
I'll be fine.
I've had a long day, though,
so I'm going to get some sleep.
Surely I'll feel better... in the morning...
after a good night's sleep...
Wh-What the hell happened to her?!
Is it because I asked her to go shopping?
Yeah, that's gotta be it!
We only got married
because the circumstances demanded it,
and making her run my errands upset her!
Mom can survive a gunshot.
Wow.
I'm in deep, deep trouble!
Any friction in our relationship jeopardizes the mission!
I need to do everything in my power
to remedy the situation!
Daddy's super wrong.
Hopefully she'll be happier in the morning.
It didn't get better.
Good morning.
G-Good morning...
Ow...
I need to brighten her mood!
Yor! Since we're both off today,
do you want to go on a date?
A d-date?!
I want to show my apprecation
for all the work you put into our relationship.
I wanna make today really special for you.
A date...
My boyfriend took me on a cruise the other day!
Have you gone on any dates recently, Yor?
Huh? No, I've never been on one.
Aren't you married?
There's no way you've never gone on a date.
Oh, uh, um...
I need to get familiar with things like dating,
or people might start suspecting
that we aren't a real family.
Oh, we don't have to go if you don't feel like it!
Let's do it!
I'm taking the opportunity
to learn as much as I can from this!
Learn?
I'll go change right away!
I wanna come!
Dates are so exciting!
Sorry, but you're staying home.
It's a date, after all.
Shock!
Sad face...
Borf...
All right, be good while we're gone.
C'mere a sec.
Listen, man! How many times do I need to say this?
I'm an informant, not your errand boy!
I don't have much of a choice.
Anya isn't allowed to be home alone,
and this is a very important mission
to ensure the stability of our family.
Didn't you say that you wanted
to create some new spy gadgets?
I've already prepared you a cheque. Here.
Can you stop giving me offers
that I can't refuse?!
All right, let's go, Yor.
Ladies first.
Last night, I came up with 862 date plans
to guarantee she has fun.
There's no way I'll fail.
Um... I'm terribly sorry, Loid...
It'll really hurt if I sit down!
Could we just go for a walk, instead?
Huh?! She's mad?!
She's still mad?!
This just ruined 794 of those plans!
O-Oh, of course.
Sure, let's go for a little stroll.
I'm worried about Mom and Dad.
Well damn, if his own kid is already worried,
it doesn't bode well for him.
Come on kiddo, let's go watch some cartoons.
Go, Bondman!
Tail the target and protect world peace!
Scruffy Head!
Huh?
I want to tail Mom and Dad!
What the hell? That sounds really freakin' cool!
Let's do it!
Let's tail them!
But your old man's pretty sharp,
so we're gonna have to be careful
and wear some disguises!
Yep!
You might be bringing even more
attention to yourself.
No problemo.
If you say so...
You've been charged with
guarding this house,
highly skilled agents of the
Secret Organization P2!
Bond, Director Chimera,
and Agent Penguinman!
Sorry about this Twilight,
but there's no way I'm missing out
on seeing your fabled charisma in action!
I can't read their minds.
They're too far away.
What are those two doing?
Is she pretending to be a spy again?
How is that even fun?
Whatever. I'll consider it as part of the mission
and pretend I don't see them.
Franky's with her,
so it's not like I have much to be concerned about.
Loid?
Oh, er, it's nothing.
More importantly,
I need to brighten her mood.
Let's see what the mall has to offer.
You have such a sleek figure, Yor.
I think these would look good on you.
How about trying it on?
If I wore something that tight,
the pressure on the wound
would definitely make me pass out.
Absolutely not.
Huh? Uh, I apologize.
Oh, my beloved!
Look me in the eyes and tell me you're lying!
Yor...
I won't let anyone else have
your beautiful, proud soul!
You're sticking out. Maybe you should sit down?
Thanks, I'm fine.
If I sit down, my butt'll hurt...
Yor, it isn't safe to stand here...
But if I sit down, my butt'll hurt!
Huh?
It's killing me!
What should I do?
I haven't been focusing on the date at all!
I've missed out on pretty much anything
Loid was trying to teach me!
What should I do?
Her mood is even worse than before!
Did she just not like my date ideas?
What is it?! What's going on in her head?!
Did I not do enough research?!
Loid always tries to act cool,
but he's absolutely choking the date right now!
What a loser!
Scruffy Head, are you always this mean?
No!
As someone who can't get any girls,
I'm well in my rights to be making fun of him!
You poor thing.
What'd you say, you little—
They're starting to get on my nerves.
It's been a long day.
How about we get dinner somewhere?
All right.
Ah, you must be Mister Forger.
Please, have a seat.
I'm terribly sorry, sir.
We have a strict dress code at our restaurant,
and we also do not allow guests under
eighteen into our establishment.
Well, you heard the guy. It's time to call it a day.
Let's head home.
I was getting kinda bored anyway.
I-Is that Briar Rose?! What the hell is she doing here?!
What's up? Needa use the bathroom or something?
There's no doubt about it.
Ow!
That's the assassin who
raided our hideout yesterday!
What's she doing here?
As the sole survivor of that tragedy,
I took it as God's mercy on my soul.
I took it as a sign to quit the underworld
and focus on supporting my girlfriend,
but this changes things!
Clearly, there's only one thing to do.
I'm gonna fucking murder her
for what she did!
There's a bad guy in the restaurant!
Die, Briar Rose!
Hurgh! I forgot you were the best assassin ever!
I am defeated!
Y-You're an assassin? Let's get a divorce.
The Forgers are done.
Let's get rid of Anya, too.
Let's get goin', kiddo.
No!
Huh? You still wanna keep playing?
My family's in danger!
Huh?
Is she worried
about her parents getting divorced or something?
She really feels that strongly
about a pretend family?
O-Okay, fine.
I'll play with you a little longer.
Okay, our next game is called "Infiltration"!
Infillytration!
Would you like an aperitif?
I'll have a glass of dry champagne.
I'll just take a cocktail. Any is fine.
Apparently they serve blowfish here,
which is a very rare delicacy from the far east.
It's included in some of their meals, too.
I-Interesting...
Blowfish is highly poisonous,
but I'm told its flesh is quite exquisite.
Pardon, could you take this
to the lady at table 3?
Right away.
Just one sip of this and you'll be
meeting your maker, Briar Rose!
Scruffy Head, hurry!
You can't rush this.
If you start getting sloppy,
they're going to take notice.
Thank you for waiting.
Oh, my. This has quite a strong smell.
And it's so thick.
Don't touch that drink, Mommy!
Huh? I feel...
I've avenged you, my brothers.
It's like the pain in my butt has gone away!
I feel so much better!
This is a woman
who'd built up an immunity to poisons.
My whole body feels a bit tingly,
but I can sit down!
I've really worked up an appetite!
I can't wait for the food to arrive.
Huh? Nice...
What just happened? Is this because of the drink?
Huh? I'm pretty sure I put in enough to kill her.
There's a fine line between poison and medicine.
Ordinary people should take recommended doses
and follow directions when taking medicine.
What's wrong?
Time to take things into my own hands.
I'll just finish her off myself!
I should be able to build a makeshift
bomb with the stuff in storage.
With that and that and that...
I won't be able to make a remote,
so I'll need to detonate it manually.
I'm sorry, Catherine.
I hope you can find it in your heart to forgive me.
We're coming up on the dining hall now.
Once we're there, I'll lower you down on a wire.
Your job will be to listen
to what they're talking about...
I should be able to make
the bomb's body with **** and ****.
I think they were stored on the right-hand shelf.
After I put in the blue ****
on the opposite shelf and some ****.
To make sure I get the most out of it,
I'll need to include ****, too!
Okay, this should work!
Damn it! What is this?
Olive oil?
Who the hell spilled all this here?
I don't have time for this, damn it!
Who the hell set up a prank like this?
This looks like the best thing
to fit my bomb in.
Actually, it might not be big enough.
Huh? Hey, wait... what?!
Why was there already a bomb in there?
And what are these? Peanuts?
A peanut bomb?!
Wait...
Are they an ally of Briar Rose?
Huh?
A kid?
Red Circus guy.
She knows who I am?
Consider this your warning.
An—We better not see your face ever again.
Got it? There won't be a next time.
You need to completely give up being a bad guy.
Make Cathurin a happy lady.
She even knows about Catherine?!
She saw right through me.
Briar Rose is a fearsome foe.
She's got such an incredible kid
working for her, too.
We live in completely different worlds.
I'm not cut out for this.
I'm going to forget this ever happened
and live a normal life.
That was an oddly noisy restaurant...
The food was delicious, though!
Indeed.
Thank goodness.
It looks like she's feeling better now.
Hopefully this ensures
the harmony of the Forgers for now.
Anya saves the day. Heh.
So, hey... Where'd you run off to earlier?
Thank you very much, Loid.
Ever since I was little, all of my time
was dedicated to taking care of my brother,
so I rarely ever had a chance to enjoy myself.
So...
I really appreciate what you've done for me today.
I'd love to do this again sometime.
When I'm not injured.
I would love to. Anytime.
Oh, look! There's a traveling
amusement park over there!
Let's check it out before it closes.
Can I ride the ferris wheel with you guys?!
I wanna come!
Hold on a sec!
What happened to tailing them?!
What the hell happened?!
The medicine—that is,
the poison—had worn off.
I don't understand women.