You lazy, lazy boy.
Anya, your teacher isn't going to be very happy
if you keep neglecting your homework.
Okie dokie.
Hide-and-seek time with Anya!
Borf!
Eek! The power went out!
I have a surprise for you, Bond!
Right this way.
I've finally found you, Number 8!
It's time for you to die!
Borf!
Bond!
Don't cry, Anya.
You made him such a happy dog.
You wanna say goodbye to me?
Borf.
I'm busy doing homework.
I don't have time to play.
Oh, no!
I'm so sorry, Bond.
I forgot to get dog food while I was out earlier.
I think Loid is going to be late tonight, too.
I'll try to make you dinner
with what we have around the house.
Borf.
All right, let's see how this goes.
Your dinner's ready, Bond!
Borf.
Bond!
Loid made me a list of all the things dogs can't eat,
so it should be a breeze!
Your dinner's ready!
Remember, if you make Mom angry she'll murder you.
Bond!
He just wouldn't eat the food I made...
What are you doing, Bond? Please calm yourself down!
Oh, no. Are you sick?
Oh, what are you doing here?
What's the matter?
Ah, thanks for finishing that one off.
I can go home early, thanks to you!
Bond!
Doggie!
Thanks!
Where'd this stray come from?
Shoo, shoo!
How dare you get food elsewhere?!
You bad boy!
A dog!
Draw eyebrows on him!
My mission tonight is to obtain
a sample of the truth serum
being developed by
Born Industries, Gerrulimus.
As usual, this was a tall order.
I didn't have enough time to gather any intel.
It must be done as soon as possible.
Disguises aren't going to work here.
I'll have to force my way in.
Borf!
What?! What is Bond doing here?!
Be quiet! You're going to get us caught.
Wait, is it just you?
Where are Yor and Anya?
Were they just taking you for a walk?
I don't know what's going on here, but you need to go!
I'm working right now!
Borf!
Borf, borf, borf!
What, you want to play?
I really don't have the time right now.
Borf! Borf!
Hey, get back here!
You're heading towards their base!
He's leading me down a deserted route?
I don't remember training him to do that...
Did he learn that prior?
Come to think of it, I remember hearing that
Born Industries was involved in Project Apple.
Did you come here because you knew that?
You're trying to get revenge for your friends
who were experimented on, aren't you?
You...
B-Borf!
All right, we can help each other here.
Since I lack intel,
relying on your sense of smell is my best option!
Borf!
This must be the lab.
There are safes everywhere.
Which one has Gerrulimus?
Their security's tight. It's going
to take a really long time to get through these.
Who knows when I'll get home?
Why the hell'd we get called back?
Apparently, they found a defect.
Shit, they're back!
I'm going to keep them busy.
You head back home!
This is going to take a while.
Borf!
Where in the world were you?
Dinner was served hours ago!
Borf! Borf!
Don't worry, boy.
Most of the staff have clocked out for the day.
Hey.
Wait...
Damn that chief.
Why the hell'd we get called back?
Apparently, they found a defect.
Our delivery date moved up, too. Give us a break.
Stop complaining.
They're getting squeezed by the higher-ups—
The door's unlocked?
What's going on here?!
"T. Bandit"?
Who's that?!
You've gotta be kidding me!
What the hell? It's right here.
All right, so which one of you—
Thanks for opening that for us!
Wh-Who the hell are you guys?! S-Someone—
Atta boy! Thanks to you,
the mission went smoother than expected.
I really didn't want to spend my entire night here.
How is it?
Borf!
Goodness, we worried ourselves sick
looking for you!
That's right! You must be really happy
that you were able to get back at Born Industries.
I'm happy to help.
All right, let's stop by the store on our way home.
I'd say you earned yourself a treat tonight!
Borf! Borf!
Lord Damian, you're gonna be late for class
if you don't get up.
As punishment for being late to class,
you are to help the Dorm Mother.
You are forbidden from leaving the grounds
until the work is completed.
This is quite unusual for you.
Though it is not a school day,
it is not elegant to live a slovenly lifestyle,
Mr. Desmond.
It won't happen again, sir.
Did you stay up to study again, Lord Damian?
I need to get more Stellas as soon as I can.
You're working way too hard.
Oh, did you know that our teacher
was going to take us to the movies today?
We might get to see
20,000 Steps under the Sea!
And on our way back, we're going
to have roast beef at Wimpsons!
You gotta finish up quick so you can come!
Yay, roast beef!
I'm not going.
I'm going to be studying in my room.
What? But it's our day off today.
You aren't going to change my mind on this.
Come on...
Can we watch whatever movie we want?
I wanna watch 20,000 Steps under the Sea.
Well, we'll see...
Come on, please? I really wanna watch it!
I'm not like them.
They aren't accomplishing anything.
I'm trying my damn best to build a future for myself.
Damian, continue working hard
so as not to shame the Desmond name.
So Father will praise me again.
You two need to get lost!
Go play somewhere else.
This is Damian's punishment.
Improper dress and eating
outside of designated hours.
As punishment, go help the Dorm Mother.
Thank you very much!
Wha—
What are you two doing here?
Why didn't you go out with the rest of them?
We're being punished.
Let's get this over with already.
I said that I'm not going to play.
Stop being so stubborn, Lord Damian!
You nerd!
You guys don't need to hang out with me.
You should go out and enjoy yourselves.
I mean, if you really think about it,
it's in very poor taste to watch a movie
on such a beautiful day.
Exactly. Doing laundry is far cooler
than what they're doing.
I mean, check this out!
We can even pretend to be Imperial Scholars!
You're gonna have to chase me
if you want your Stellas!
That cape belongs to me, you jerk!
Get back here and do your jobs!
Elegant.
The companionship is so preciously elegant.
Now that's the face of a boy
who's yearning for a picnic!
I am not!
Hm.
So you've chosen to slack off
instead of focusing on your work?
You three clearly need to be punished further!
What?!
You are to complete field research
with Mr. Green, our guidance counselor.
Enjoyin' the outdoors, lads?!
I'm gonna die!
You don't even have to leave the premises
for a boat ride!
Don't you just love this place?
We're going to die!
Don't worry, lads. I was in the navy,
so I know my way around a boat!
Just relax and have fun!
All right! We should be able to make it
to the lake from here.
It's a great spot to relax!
Moderate exercise is good for the brain, too!
Just sitting at your desk isn't always
the best way to study!
This isn't exactly moderate!
Come on, lads!
If you don't start picking up your slack,
we're going to crash into that rock!
Sir, there's a waterfall ahead!
Lord Damian!
Save me!
I'm the second son
of the Desmond family!
I'll save you!
Uh, lads?
I'm the heir to the Elman family!
I'm the successor to the Egeburg fam—
Y-You need to survive at all costs!
He's right!
Go on and make the world a better place!
You guys...
Get to the boat!
I don't know how much longer we can hold you!
Damn it!
I can see you're having fun,
but you can stand here.
The current isn't even fast.
Huh?
It was only fast because I was paddling.
All right lads, gather up some firewood
before you catch a cold.
Yes, sir!
Finally.
I've gotten kinda hungry after all that.
Since you're already wet,
you may as well go catch some fish.
Wait, did you not pack a lunch for us?
Why would I do something like that?
You're Eden students!
Everything you need is right here.
A-Are you serious?
I'll get you some hunting materials.
You figure out the best way to use them!
What the heck...
It's so good!
Indeed!
Ain't it, though?
The roast beef at Wimpsons is good
in its own way,
but it'll never beat prey you catch yourself.
I didn't think it would taste so good!
Yum!
What's so fun about this?
While everyone else is studying,
we've accomplished absolutely nothing here.
Doesn't the gentle breeze feel nice, lads?
The way our shadows dance around the campfire,
the breeze through the trees,
the smell of fresh soil.
There's nothing wrong with taking a moment
to unwind and appreciate your surroundings.
I won't become an Imperial Scholar
by spacing out here.
Oh, yeah? Well, did you know
that modern studies in neuroscience
suggest that your brain is
revitalized when you're spacing out?
Apparently, it affects
your memory and imagination.
A lot of artists and athletes make an effort
to give themselves ample time to daydream.
Who knows? Maybe a little bit of daydreaming
is all you need to get those Stellas.
That sounds silly!
Daydream...
Daydream, daydream, daydream...
That doesn't really count as daydreaming,
Lord Damian...
He might not be as bright as I thought.
All right.
It seems like your clothes have dried up.
Why don't we take a walk to the lake?
Apparently,
students have been calling it "Stella Lake."
Stella! Let's go!
Lord Damian, you're way too obsessed with Stellas.
Pic-pic-pic-pic-picnic!
Oh, that reminds me.
I heard that people in the south
have been using "picnic" as a code word
for defecting to the West.
Wait, is that where you're trying to take us?!
A couple kilometers
isn't taking you to the border.
I wonder why they go to the West.
I wonder if the sweets taste better
in the West.
That's a good question.
Why would you want to leave
such a beautiful night sky behind?
There's nothing to worry about!
Once Lord Damian becomes an adult,
Ostania'll be even better!
Hey!
Oh, you want to become a politician?
That's quite interesting.
Well, I'm trying to be like my father...
I see. Having a goal to work towards
is always a wonderful thing.
When I'm older, I wanna be a cosmonaut!
Is it? Well, that's cool!
When I'm older, I...
have no idea!
Oh, you don't, eh?
Well, that's perfectly fine.
Actually, I want to try
a bunch of different sweets!
Good stuff! Really aiming high.
You'll have to think earnestly
about how to make that possible.
How are you going to stay healthy
if all you're eating is sweets?
Aw, man.
And we're here.
Wow, the way the stars reflect on the water
makes it look like outer space!
Take a look, lads. Here,
you actually can reach for the stars.
That was terrible!
Do you still regret coming?
No.
I think this is beautiful.
Indeed.
It's beautiful.
The universe is such a vast place.
Yeah.
The stars kinda look like sugar
spread all over the night sky, if you ask me.
Of course you would say that!
Lord Damian laughed.
Whatever, shut up.
Time to start heading back, lads!
Oh, yeah. You were supposed
to be doing field research.
Make sure you three write reports.
Ugh, I wanted to shower and sleep
when we got back.
Great attention to hygiene, laddie!
Master Henderson.
I've brought the boys' reports.
Thank you, Mr. Green.
Were they able to spread their wings?
I sure hope so.
Quite elegant.
We saw a lot and did a bunch of stuff. It was fun.
But he'll have to work on his spelling.