The targets are approaching the room.
Three of them.
The two in the back sound like heavyweights.
They're avoiding all windows and doors.
Judging by their movements,
they're definitely pros.
Conrad is sitting on the sofa next to the wall.
All right, let's see what you've brought for me.
You'll get your payment after.
Y-You better hold up your end of the deal.
This is, without a doubt, the data
I've been looking for. All right, as promised...
The deal is underway.
All right, we're heading in.
Yuri.
Roger.
We're with the State Security Service.
You're all being detained under the suspicion
of being spies.
Damn it!
Move!
Hello there, you traitorous scum!
We have a wonderful cell
with your name on it,
so please accompany us
to the station.
Excellent work, Second Lieutenant Briar.
Thank you very much.
We need you to take care
of this fellow next.
Have you heard about the various
books and articles going around
in the West that mock and slander Ostania?
It's nothing but bold-faced lies
and conspiracy theories.
A lot of them are made by shady printing presses
here in Ostania
and are sold to the West.
And among the writers, this guy popped up.
Franklin Perkin. Age 39.
He was a journalist
during the previous administration,
and was arrested
for aiding anti-government extremists.
I want you to follow him
and get the evidence we need,
along with the names of whoever buys
his propaganda.
As ridiculous as these articles are,
there are plenty of idiots in
the West who'll believe them.
I want him dealt with
before this reaches public consciousness.
Yes, sir!
Aren't we working Yuri a bit too hard?
I'll be just fine!
Selling out your own country
to make a quick buck...
Just the fact that my sister
breathes the same air as this scum...
is all the motivation I need.
Observation of subject
J-095: Franklin Perkin.
On the 6th, subject wakes at 07:21.
Subject watches the television
program Good Morning Ostania.
Subject curses at the newscaster.
08:10, subject leaves
for job at the post office.
See appendices for details of his attire.
Subject rides on third car of the U-8 train.
See appendices for descriptions
of fellow passengers.
At 12:06, subject goes to the
restaurant Fjord with coworker M.
Orders lunch Set A.
See appendices for log
of conversation topics.
At 17:49, subject leaves work
and goes to central market.
At noon today,
the 12th Annual International Education
Symposium was held in Frejis.
At 18:33, subject returns home
and watches television programs
News 20 and Berlint in Love.
Subject appears infatuated
with the female lead.
No further noteworthy activities
before retiring for the night.
You sure didn't hold back on the details.
Leave this to me!
You've been doing this for two days straight.
You should get some rest.
Oh, this is nothing.
Here's my next report.
"On the 7th, at 08:07,
subject goes to work."
"Has lunch at the restaurant
Fjord and orders lunch Set B..."
"Fjord."
"Yor."
You're clearly tired. Get some rest.
No. That always happens.
Open up, Mr. Perkin! I know you're in there!
H-Hey there, miss.
How many times do I need
to tell you to pay your rent?
Could I just have a bit more time?
That's what you told me last time.
All right then, two more days!
I promise I'll get it to you by then.
This is your last chance.
Next time, you're getting evicted!
Stupid landlady.
Heading out for a bit, Dad.
There's some leftover food here if you get hungry.
All right. See you later.
Does he think he's being followed?
That, or he's looking for something to write about.
Our country must face this with resolve!
Yeah! That's right!
Let's teach the West a lesson!
Not a single good story in sight.
Check out this cool Bondman pistol I got!
No way! Can I give it a try?
Get outta here!
Meanie!
Huh? Hey!
My pistol!
Overcome by poverty, street children
desperately dig through trash for scraps.
Not bad.
What the heck is wrong with you?!
We're gonna tell the Secret Police on you!
Listen closely,
you greedy little upper-class snot-nosed brat.
People whose ideals lean toward
the West, like yourself...
are the ones who are going to get arrested
and killed.
That bastard!
I'm gonna execute him!
Don't.
First, we need to find out
who's buying his underground publications.
They're going to love this one!
Frank.
Dad?
You haven't gotten involved
with the wrong people again, right?
I-I haven't. Leave me alone!
If it wasn't for your odd sense of justice,
you could've kept your job at the paper.
What's so wrong about trying to improve
the lives of the people I love?
Even now, we scrimp and save
just to keep living paycheck to paycheck.
If we had money, Mom would've...
Hey, Frank...
Just forget about it!
On the 11th at 08:36,
subject leaves for work.
He's had no interactions so far
that would give us a lead on his buyers.
Which means...
he does it at work?
Here's all the mail that's been inspected!
Thanks!
Good work.
I'll take care of those, Joseph.
Go ahead and get some lunch.
Oh, thanks!
What should I have today?
So he's been slipping them in
after they've passed inspection.
If you do this,
you won't like what happens next.
On the 15th at 08:02.
I'm heading to work.
All right.
The State Security... Service.
Sorry, Dad. I might not be back for a while.
Franklin Perkin.
I believe you're the one who wrote this?
We've already arrested the buyer
this was addressed to.
Surrender.
I appreciate you waiting outside for me.
Who knew State Security officers
could be so kind?
It's so your family doesn't have
to see how much of a lowlife you are.
Don't get the wrong idea.
I'm trying to fight a corrupt government,
while you serve as its lapdog.
Who's actually the lowlife here?
I would never do anything
to cause my family concern.
Ever.
I'll request that your father
receive some financial aid to get by.
I appreciate it.
Hello there, Yuri!
Chief!
You've been working hard!
I'm happy to hear it.
I'm honored, sir.
This must be rather difficult work for a newbie.
Don't let the stress build up.
Oh, no.
I think I'm quite well-suited for this job!
I'll use this momentum to capture Twilight
and protect the peace of this nation!
Well, that'd be just great.
If you do, I'll treat you
to one of my favorite meat places.
Really?! I'm gonna hold you to it!
Coming!
Hiya, Yor!
Yuri? What are you doing here
so late at night?
Unkie?
Good evening, Yuri.
Why are you here, Forger?!
Pick up a night shift, or something!
Did something happen?
I was just feeling a bit homesick, is all.
Why are you pestering me, pooch?
I'm sure you've had a long day at work,
so why don't I make us some tea?
Yor, Yor...
Yor, Yor, Yor, Yor, Yor, Yor, Yor, Yor, Yor!
Yor!
Yuck...
We're going to get a noise complaint
if you don't calm down!
My name is Bondman!
I'll take it from here.
You go on ahead, Agent M!
No!
I don't want to lose you!
M...
I'll do whatever it takes
to stay with you, Bondman.
Time to get out of here!
My spotless suit.
My beloved, gleaming silver car.
The techniques I mastered through countless
battles, and my gentlemanly demeanor...
Oh, you're such a masterful driver!
I love you, Bondman!
Since I'm the coolest and so clever,
romance comes naturally.
My country has been at odds with yours
for as long as I can remember.
If you keep getting in my way,
I won't show you mercy.
How fickle.
We're all just humans
trying to live on the same planet.
Why do we need to fight over
something as petty as a line on a map?
Then why don't you stop this conflict?!
The peace treaty has been signed!
The boundaries that once separated us
are no more.
You're amazing, Bondman!
I'll never let you go!
My father's obsessed with
creating this Destroyer Bomb!
Please stop him, Bondman!
But of course, Gina!
Oh, thank you so much, Bondman!
Once my father wakes up,
I'd love to introduce you to him!
I'd love to, Gina.
My terrorist boyfriend
was arrested because of you!
You won't get away with this!
Revenge won't relieve your pain,
but I believe my love just might.
We won't stop until we've taken over the world!
Never mind all that. Let's go out on a date.
Hello, Bondman.
I'm here to collect this month's rent.
Also, there are noise complaints
from the neighbors.
Well, hello there!
You're looking as beautiful as ever, miss.
Hey! What's with all these broads?!
Pick one already, damn it!
How many of us are you dating?!
You cheater!
I'm going to make every last
lady in this world happy!
Dealing with risk is just a part of the job.
Next time on Spy Wars: "Bondman Returns!"
This must be one of those flirting stories.
Now I can talk with Becky about it.
I think I've become a real grown-up.
Don't say that.
How was anything he did gentlemanly?
I wanna ride the panda!
I cannot comprehend the appeal
of riding these ever-popular pandas.
Why do children insist on riding this thing?
It's slow and extremely boring.
Plus, it feels like deliberate government
brainwashing intended to null the brain
of the passenger
making them an unwavering puppet of their—
I wanna ride it!
Let's let her ride it, Loid.
Was that fun?
I wanna ride it again!
I don't understand children.
The Silt Seashore is where people go
to make the most of their summer!
I wanna go to the beach!
Well, we can't go to the beach,
but we can go to a pool.
Pool!
I'm so glad she's enjoying herself.
Oops, I just peed a little.
Not like anyone's going to find out, though.
I feel so much better.
I'm never going in a pool again.
What?! But it looked like she was enjoying herself!
I don't understand children.
Time to get up, Lord Damian.
You don't wanna miss roll call again, do you?
Huh?
Lord Damian!
You were already awake?
Yeah, about an hour ago.
I was reviewing my notes.
It's pretty rare that I oversleep.
Impressive as ever!
Wake up, Anya!
You've only got ten minutes
until your bus gets here!
Anya has ten more minutes
until the explosion...
Anya will stop it...
Come on, wake up!
We can't afford another Tonitrus Bolt!