Oh, Vincent!
I love you!
We can't do this, Sonia.
My betrothed is still waiting
for me in the West...
But your parents decided on her,
didn't they?
I'll make you forget about her!
We can't do this, Sonia!
I can't breathe...
Oh, Anya!
I just so happened to be in the neighborhood
and was wondering if I could swing by!
Oh, I can? Sounds good, I'll see you soon!
Good day, Anya!
Home alone? Probably not, right?
Were you also out learning teleportation
from Shwoop-man?
Today's the day I finally
meet my precious Loid
and propose that we begin courtship!
You mustn't commit adultery, my lady.
Daddy, Becky came for a visit.
Hey there. Welcome.
It's really him!
Go on and introduce yourself, my lady.
U-Um... H-H-Hello.
Thank you for having me over.
I apologize for the intrusion, Mr. Forger.
Oh, it's no problem at all.
It's good that she gets to play
with her friends every so often.
It's nice to see you, Becky.
Thank you for always being such
good friends with my daughter.
Asterisk, tic-tac-toe, triangle,
smiley old guy, steam, heart?
Some kind of code?!
Please get up, my lady.
You're at someone else's house.
Please have some manners.
Love...
I feel like I've seen this somewhere before...
I trust you'll be on your best behavior, my lady.
I'll pick you up
when it's time to go home.
Thank you for taking care of her.
Of course.
The way her attendant
carries herself is quite peculiar.
She's clearly a highly-experienced
former soldier.
I guess that's to be expected
of the Blackbells.
Want me to show you around?
Oh yeah, I've never been here before, have I?
This is the living room!
What? This isn't just the storage
space by your front door?
This is my room!
Oh, this is even more compact
than my little Wiesel's doghouse.
Isn't it hard to breathe in here?
Let's stop exploring.
Really? Why?
By the way, where's your mother?
Mommy's out walking Bond.
This is my chance!
Oh, my precious Loid!
We can't do this, Becky! I have a wife.
But your parents decided on this marriage,
didn't they?
But...
With me around,
I'll make you forget about her!
Oh, Becky!
Becky wants to become my mom?!
I'm sure Anya would be happy
if I were her mother, too.
Why don't we move out of that
cramped little apartment?
A castle!
Come, Anya. Today we'll be going
to school by helicopter.
I love you, Mommy!
We'll have the finest dinners
made by world-class chefs.
Delicious!
Yum.
Since we have servants,
you don't have to bother doing housework anymore!
Why don't we go out and do something?
Yay!
She makes a good point!
I'm sorry, Mommy.
Becky's won me over with the allure
of world-class chefs.
Daddy! You should play with us, too!
Nice assist, Anya!
Er, play?
W-W-W-We can just chat.
U-Um... M-My...
Mwy name is Becky Blackbell!
Hm? Yes, I know that.
World-class chefs! World-class chefs!
After all, the Blackbells are quite well-known.
I knew about you even before
you were in Anya's class.
As an important source of information.
He's known about me for that long?!
I have multiple avenues to obtain intel,
but there might be some useful information
I can gain from her as well.
Maybe I'll probe a bit.
Daddy always goes straight into work mode.
How is your father doing?
I heard he's been busy with the
restructuring going on in the industry.
Y-Yes, he is. But he's still nice to me!
Whenever he has a day off,
he makes sure he plays with me.
We went to the movies last time!
Maybe next time I could go with you?
Oh, really? What did you go see?
Did you go to the theater by the river?
There are a lot of great
restaurants around there.
The time her father is off from work,
the range of his activities,
his habits, what he likes to eat...
Plenty of potentially useful information.
Oh, um... We saw a romance...
Is he trying to figure out my preferences?!
He mentioned restaurants...
Wait, is he trying to ask me out?!
He just asked me out, didn't he?!
You two must be really close.
Do you go out with your family often?
Is there anything you do with your father at home?
Currently, there's nothing suggesting
that Blackbell Heavy Industries
is involved in any plans for war,
but it wouldn't hurt to obtain some
information for the future just in case.
M-M-My dad loves playing chess.
I don't know how it works,
but sometimes I play with him!
Uh, and...
He's asking so much about my family!
Could it be that he's
actually trying to envision a future with me?!
He's looking at me so intently!
She's wild.
I'm back from the walk.
Borf!
Oh? Welcome, Becky!
My romantic rival makes her appearance!
World-class chefs! World-class chefs!
World-class chefs!
Right when Loid started taking an interest in me!
H-Hello, Mrs. Forger.
Oh, how sweet of you.
Behold, Becky! This is our dog, Bond!
Borf!
I just know I was on the verge
of winning him over!
Behold, Becky!
Just one more push, Becky!
Fight like your life depends on it!
Use what you've learned from all those dramas!
Oh, Loid.
I bought the ingredients you asked for.
Thanks, Yor.
Playing the housewife card, is she?
Hmph, how naïve.
As if you would win over my beloved Loid like that.
Daddy and Mommy are already married, though.
As Jonathan from Berlint in Love said,
even a married man
craves the companionship of a woman.
Huh? That wasn't much of a reaction.
Maybe I didn't flutter my eyelashes enough.
But I thought Tommy said it drives them wild
when a girl lets down her hair.
I heard that Becky has been looking forward
to meeting you, Loid.
She must be very happy to see you.
Perhaps this is how she expresses that.
Uh, right.
I've made us some tea.
Why don't you have a seat beside Becky, Loid?
He's right next to me!
What do I do? What do I do?!
Showing mercy by having him sit next to me?
What is Mrs. Forger playing at?
I know. She must've admitted defeat
after seeing my hair attack!
This is your chance, Becky!
Go all in!
She doesn't seem to be feeling well.
E-Excuse me, sweetheart.
Can we revisit our conversation from earlier?
Are you interested in my family?
What did she call me?
Oh, sorry. It was just
something I was curious about.
Your family is quite famous, after all.
I didn't think she'd notice,
but I guess I went too far.
What?! You were just toying with me all that time?!
What are you talking about?
Yor's going to get the wrong idea.
Oh, Loid! How sweet of him to entertain Becky
while I was gone.
He's so kind.
Wipe that smile off your face!
She's so sure she's won!
Do I really not have a chance with him?
Are my chefs going to lose?
Fine, I guess I'll pull out my trump card!
I'll use the final attack that
Penelope used on Tommy!
Oh, dear. I think I'm getting a little drunk.
Uh, it's tea.
According to Berlint in Love,
this is a last-ditch effort that guarantees
he'll fall for you!
There's no turning back now!
You've lost, Forger.
Er, Yor, this isn't...
Oh, no!
I've somehow managed to put
alcohol in a child's drink!
What do I do?!
No, really. It's just tea.
Did I steep the tea leaves for too long?!
We're leaving!
Let's go to the hospital!
Hey, wait!
Yor?!
What are your symptoms, Becky?!
Do you feel nauseous?!
I'm fine! I'm fine, really! Just put me down!
Never underestimate acute alcohol poisoning!
You've got it all wrong!
I'm not sure exactly what kind
of doctor should see you!
You need medical attention more than I do!
We're almost there! Hang in there!
You'll die if you fall asleep!
I'm pretty sure I won't!
"Hee-hee-hoo!" Like that! "Hee-hee-hoo!"
That's not it, either!
Please wait, ma'am...
I guess I'll tell you...
I was lying because I wanted
to date your husband!
I'm not drunk!
I'm so sorry! I'm so sorry!
I'm so happy you're all right.
Huh?
Can you stand?
Y-You're not going to yell at me?
Why would I? You're safe and sound.
No, I mean the thing I told you about...
I'm beyond delighted to know about
how appreciated Loid is.
He's such a lovely person.
Sh-She's actually a really nice person!
Is she okay with infidelity?
I'm the one who should be sorry.
I took you this far because I panicked.
No, that's my fault.
Sometimes I wonder how Loid
keeps putting up with me.
B-But he chose you, didn't he?
How did you manage to pierce his heart?
I want to know!
Pierce his... what?
I would never shoot Loid!
And I don't know how to use a bow and arrow.
Huh?
What?
Oh, I think the reason Loid chose me is, um...
I can't tell her that our priorities aligned.
My memories are a bit fuzzy,
but if I remember correctly...
It's because I'm strong.
Because you're strong?!
Loid prefers stronger women?
Well, she's definitely pretty strong.
Like, she was just hit by a car.
Hey! There they are.
Becky!
Becky, you forgot your bag.
My beloved got so worried
that he came looking for me?!
Your bag.
He likes strong women.
What can I do to show him I'm strong?
There must be something...
Perfect!
Oh, I suddenly feel like
I want to throw down a hammer!
What kind of feeling is that?
I really don't understand spoiled rich kids.
May I have a try, mister?
You gotta pay if you wanna try, missy.
Chefs! Chefs! Chefs! Chefs! Chefs! Chefs!
Here I go!
Che—
You give up?
I wasn't strong enough.
He'll never love someone as weak as me...
A-Are you all right?!
I'll never win Loid over in this state.
Oh, maybe she wanted to give Loid the top prize.
I'm going to borrow this for a second.
Hup.
First place! First place! First place!
I-I did it...
I overdid it again...
So this is strength...
Is this what it looks like when he's
starstruck by a strong woman?!
I guess he really
does like strong women after all.
Yor...
You've got the wrong idea, Loid!
I used to be the apprentice of
a professional hammer user!
Just look at his beautiful, round eyes!
He's definitely in love with her!
I guess I'm no match for you, Mrs. Forger.
Huh?
You're as gentle as a ray of sunshine,
and mightier than the earth below.
You're the perfect lady.
I want to become your apprentice!
I want to become strong like you!
L-Like me?
All right. Let's train together!
Yes, ma'am!
And maybe some day, Loid'll look my way.
I've come to get you, my lady.
Not like that, Becky.
You need to twist your hips more!
Ah, déjà vu...
Yeah, Mommy's way more fun to be around.
Excuse me Dr. Forger, weren't you going
on vacation as of tomorrow?
Yes, my apologies.
Don't worry about it.
You're long overdue for a vacation, anyway.
Hope you get some well-deserved rest.
That sounds really nice.
Tell me how it goes when you get back!
Sure. Thank you very much.
I'm sorry you'll have to pick up my slack,
but I appreciate it nonetheless.
That's the basic rundown of this mission.
Do you have any questions?
No, I'll be fine.
I'm counting on you, Nightfall.
Oh, and...
Take a look at this, too.
I was planning to give that mission to Twilight
once he got back from vacation,
but things have changed.
Sorry, but this is urgent.
Will you be able to take this on?
Of course, I'll also split the tasks
with some other agents.
No, I can do all of this myself.
I appreciate your enthusiasm,
but you have your own mission, as well.
I don't intend to destroy
all of you with overwork.
I just don't believe anyone else
will be able to fulfill these tasks.
Fine. But don't push yourself too hard.
Agent Twilight is the best spy WISE has to offer.
Every mission that he's tasked with
is one that no other spy is capable of.
But for me, this is a huge opportunity.
Twilight has taught me
a lot over our relationship.
Skills that you should know for the job,
and how to use them to gain the upper hand.
I get to fully utilize everything he's taught me
to finish the mission.
Once I complete the mission
making use of Twilight's complete skillset...
I'm going to become his wife.
All right. Now I'm absolutely positive
he'll realize that I'm the best one for him!
And yet...
This still isn't enough
to ensure complete victory.
In order to defeat Yor Briar...
In order to become Mrs. Forger...
I need more!
More!
Those'll get you up to speed on what's happened
to your patients while you were gone.
Thanks.
Three days later and Twilight is
as lovely as ever. I love you so much.
How was your vacation? Anything new?
Like maybe a relationship issue
that I could exploit?
There were a handful of issues
like Anya being selfish
and the whole bomb threat, but...
No, not really.
I see.
Tch.
What about you?
Did anything happen while I was gone?
I worked very hard on my missions
so I can be a woman you'd admire.
Next time, I'll outperform your wife, too.
So you should pick me instead of her!
No, not really.
I see.
Nightfall did?
Yes.
She was determined to take it all on herself.
She did excellent work.
To think that Nightfall would take over
for me while I was gone.
I'm sure she had her own missions, too.
By the way, I had some remaining souvenirs
from my vacation.
Would you like them?
She's glaring at me so hard!
Huh? Wait, why?!
Thank you very much.
Please excuse me.
I wuv you! I wuv you! I wuv you!
I figured that was my only chance
to say anything, so I did.
I see.
Oh, Fiona.
Good morning.