In an era where the nations of the world
are silently fighting a war of intelligence,
two countries were at odds with
each other: Ostania, in the east,
and Westalis, in the west.
In order to keep an eye on the actions of
a leading figure in Ostania's government,
Westalis set Operation Strix in motion.
The one tasked with this operation
is the skilled agent, Twilight.
The mission given to the master of
disguise with a hundred faces was...
to start a family.
The father, Loid Forger, is a psychiatrist.
His true identity: a spy.
Code name: Twilight.
The mother, Yor Forger, is a civil
servant who works at city hall.
Her true identity: an assassin.
Code name: Briar Rose.
The daughter, Anya Forger.
Her true identity: a telepath
who can read people's minds.
The dog, Bond Forger.
His true identity: a canine seer
who can see the future.
As they maintain the facade
of an ordinary family life,
they continue to fight their own battles
behind closed doors.
Bond, we're going for a walk.
Borf.
Borf!
You wanna come?
I'm not going.
Bhork!
I'm busy right now.
Difficulty level max.
Origami?
Apparently, it's very popular
at school right now.
She's really giving it her all.
If she isn't coming,
I guess I'll do some training with Bond instead.
All right. We're off.
Have a nice time, you two.
Go!
That's right.
You want to aim for places
that'll immobilize the suspect.
Stay away from vital points that'd
cause fatal wounds.
I can't extract information
from a fatally wounded suspect.
What the hell, man!
Have you forgotten how much I've done for you?!
Hey!
Once you've got them,
hold on like your life depends on it!
It puts you at risk, too. Once you let go,
the suspect can retaliate against you.
Maybe you're too nice. You don't seem
to do well with barking and biting.
You know...
Why do I gotta play the suspect, anyway?!
Again, I'm an informant, and—
Well, I need to train him. I have no other choice.
How am I your only option?!
Well, go on! Tell me in 500 characters or less!
Things are becoming especially uncertain now,
so I need to prepare for the worst.
That literally answered nothing!
All right. That's enough suppression
and protection training.
Let's move on to scent training
and locating explosives.
It's really hard to learn.
Wait, am I supposed to participate?
Am I supposed to be the bomber?
What's wrong?
Are you already feeling tired?
Project Apple was where they ran experiments
to turn dogs into killing machines, right?
He's probably traumatized by the training
he went through.
I see.
Is there anything this useless mutt can do?
This project was a complete failure.
The test subjects will need to be disposed of.
To him, playing and training are no different.
You need to make it fun for him.
You've never really been good at that.
Take him on a walk or something
for a change of pace.
So yeah, I'm going home.
Hey!
Guess we can go for a walk.
Borf!
Wow, you've made so many!
Those little stars are so cute.
Tsk, tsk, tsk. These are no ordinary stars.
"Anya Forger! I present you with this Stella!"
Yeah!
Don't eat stuff off the ground.
My ice cream! I barely even got to have any...
What a loser! From now on,
your name's gonna be Icesplatio.
No!
Double-scoop ice cream!
Can't believe this guy gets more than us.
Borf!
Ah, so you were protecting his food. Good boy!
I knew you were the right dog for us!
Hey!
What does this thing want from me?!
It's probably after my ice cream!
What's gotten into you, Bond?!
My ice cream! I barely even got to have any...
I'm really sorry about that!
I'll buy you another one.
Three scoops! Three scoops!
Lucky.
Three more scoops?
It's unlike you to lose your cool
over someone else's food.
Why would you do that? Are you hungry?
Hurgh!
Dear God, what have I done?!
Someone call an ambulance!
What's going on with you today?!
Somebody get this thing off me!
I'm so sorry!
He's been acting weird all day today.
You clearly haven't trained him properly!
Biting a random civilian is unacceptable.
This isn't going to go unpunished.
Great work, Bond. You saved the world.
Borf!
Borf...
This doesn't make any sense.
I've given him plenty of training
on basic socialization and being obedient.
He's never been the type to attack people, either.
Much like Anya, I still have a lot to learn about him.
Oh, come on. This is my favorite dress!
That's it, I'm done with you.
You're going back to the pound!
Is he sick?
Maybe I should take him to the vet.
Daisy!
Please, back up! It isn't safe here!
But Daisy's trapped in there!
No! Daisy!
What's the matter?
He's really on edge today.
Would you give it a rest?!
Borf!
Smoke?
Someone call the fire department!
The fire's spreading faster than expected!
A fire?
Was he reacting to the smell?
Is there anyone inside?
Nope. Thankfully, everyone made it out.
There's been a lot of these lately.
I've heard rumors that it's actually an arsonist.
Where's that fire truck?!
Daisy! Daisy!
Wha—
What are you doing? It's been cleared out!
It ain't safe in there, y'know!
Wait. Did he catch someone's scent?
Bond! Bond!
Bond!
That's hot! What the hell are you doing?!
A puppy? Was it left behind?
You're ridiculous, you know that?
We need to get out of here, though.
Can you run?
Stay as low as you can!
That was our way out...
He's clearly scared of the fire.
We can't force our way through.
This is bad. What do we do?
The bottom floor
is completely engulfed in flames.
Our only choice is the northern fire escape.
There's a chance it collapses,
but at least we'll be out.
Go, Bond!
What are you doing?
This isn't the time to mess around!
Th-That was close.
Your sense of smell works at a time like this?
That's quite impressive.
I guess the fire escape is a no-go.
Our only choice is to force our way
through the smoke.
That'd be fine for me, but Bond's running out of air.
A plastic bag...
All right, so we'll capture
some of the clean air down here...
and now we've got a makeshift oxygen tank.
If you're having trouble breathing,
make use of this.
Borf.
It'll be easier if we put her in here.
It's time to go.
Follow me as closely as you can!
Borf!
Let's go!
I can't believe y'all made it outta there!
Apparently, he caught the scent
of a puppy in apartment 407.
Oh, that's Ms. Bennett's puppy!
I guess she didn't get out in time.
He really did all that just for her?
Pretty special pup you've got there.
Bond! You're on fire! Fire!
Holy smokes! Lemme getcha a bucket of water!
What a skinny lil' guy!
Are you really that skinny under all that?
Bond is always bathed by Yor,
so I've never seen him like this.
No, Twilight. Don't do this.
You are a cool-headed spy.
Do not let your emotions show.
That was a pretty close call.
What's the matter?
Hey!
Sir, can you look after that puppy?
S-Sure...
Get back here, Bond!
I fuckin' love how it burns!
Daisy!
Please, back up! It isn't safe here!
But Daisy's still inside!
It just keeps getting better!
Wh-What the hell is that ugly lookin' thing?!
Let go of me, you stupid mutt!
He's biting people again?
I'll make you regret that!
Oil and ignition tools?
Learn your fuckin' place, you dumbass dog!
You knew he was the arsonist?
They've found this same oil
across multiple other arson cases.
I'll report him to the police
and let them deal with it.
I'm surprised you noticed.
Did you notice his scent back there?
Or was he letting off a particular smell?
Well, either way, well done.
Oh, thank goodness, Daisy!
I'm so glad you're safe!
I don't know what I would've done if I lost you.
I'm so sorry, Daisy...
She wouldn'ta made it
without that heroic passerby and his dog!
Truly commendable stuff, I tell ya.
Where'd they get off to? I'll go find 'em.
We should get going.
I'm not really interested in seeing our faces in the paper.
The best boy of the day
gets to enjoy a year's worth of meat!
You did a good job today. I'm proud.
But...
I told you to bite their arm, not their leg!
Don't push yourself too hard.
There's someone back home
who'd be heartbroken if you died.
I'm sorry, too.
I shouldn't be working you so hard.
It's much more important
that you feel like you're a part of the Forgers.
Sound good?
Are you hurt at all?
You probably inhaled a lot of smoke.
Let's have you checked out just in case.
What are you doing?
Hey, stop that!
Don't get the wrong idea.
It's critical to the mission
that I ensure the stability of the Forgers.
I don't have work tomorrow,
so why don't we go to a dog park?
I feel bad for having to leave you behind
while we were on vacation.
Why does your bark change when you're wet?
I did it!
Is it a knife?
Huh? I-It's a penguin...
Maybe I'm not the best at this.
Oh, I know. How about something like this?
Ta-da!
Ooh!
Oh, dear. I might've made a couple wrong cuts...
We're back.
Welcome home.
B-Bond! You've shrunk down to almost nothing!
Oh, dear. What happened?
It's a funny story.
Someone accidentally sprayed
water on him on our way home.
Oh, I see.
His voice is different, too?!
Don't worry, Anya.
This is just what happens when he gets wet.
Once he dries, he'll be back to his usual fluffy self.
It's not like I can tell them that he rescued
a puppy from a fire and caught an arsonist.
They were doing good deeds, too?
I'll dry you right off, Bond. I'll be right back.
Thanks, Yor.
Daddy!
Daddy and Bond,
I present you with this Stella!
What's this? You made Stellas for us?
It's the award given
to awesome hardworkin' walkers.
Wow, congratulations, you two!
That's sweet and all,
but could you get some real Stellas?
Shock!
All right. Let's get dinner going.
I'll help.
I wanna eat Daddy's Salisbury steak!