The Pastry of Knowledge.
Tales of this pastry have been passed on
as it became one of the Seven Wonders of Eden.
A mysterious pâtissier appears unannounced at
their cafeteria and serves this pastry on a whim.
Not only are they delicious,
but students who taste these pastries
also end up becoming Imperial Scholars.
Rumors started to spread that eating them
guaranteed your success as a student.
As a result, Eden students started doing
everything they could to get their hands on one.
Oh, my! Is that you, my sweet prince?
No, I'm your clone.
That simply cannot be!
Those eyes! That hair!
Ah, I love you my sweet prince!
No, I'm a female sheep just like you.
Oh, dang it! The story hasn't progressed at all!
It's a complete mess!
I mean, these look exactly the same.
You should use your imagination a bit.
Now it's my turn.
It'll be a battle story
about twins separated at birth.
No way! If it's too rough, these'll get all torn up.
Shock.
By the way, did you hear?
Next term, we're going to be split up
depending on our grades.
What's that mean?
It means...
There's me, who's decent at school,
and then there's you,
who's terrible at school.
Depending on how it goes,
we may not be in the same class anymore.
Shock!
I'll be all alone!
You will! That's why you need to
give all your classes your best shot!
On top of our midterms and finals,
I hear our quiz tomorrow will
be a huge deciding factor,
just like our test on classic literature.
This is gonna be rough!
It's so over for me.
Th-Th-Th-This is huge!
It's happening! He appeared!
What? What happened?
That dessert is being made in the cafeteria!
What are you talkin' about?
Do you seriously not know?!
That highly-skilled pâtissier came
and made the dessert everyone talks about!
It's the Pastry of Knowledge!
The dessert that's fabled to turn
whoever eats it into an Imperial Scholar!
He made macarons this year.
There's a limited supply,
so we gotta get them while they last!
O-Okay!
I'm not missing my chance to become a genius!
I mean, I'm sure it's just a silly rumor,
but what if it's actually true this time?
Besides, macarons made by a royal chef?
I'd want to eat them just for that!
It sounds delicious!
What's a macaron?
That's the place!
We need to hurry before they run out!
Gah!
Second Son.
Shrimp!
What are you in such a hurry for?
Shut up! Right back at you!
There's only one order
of Pierre Pommier's new sweets left!
First come, first served!
Those macarons are as good as mine!
That isn't all that's on the line!
Your last plate, please.
You got it.
Sorry folks, we've sold our entire stock!
It's my lucky day!
I hope this'll help me get a Stella!
How exciting!
George...
Huh?
Hand it over, that's mine!
Give me that! I need them more than they do!
Wah! I'm being mugged!
I bought these with what little money I have!
You can't have them!
That's right! You never
gave me back my pen case!
Huh?
And you embarrassed me by making me sing
when I didn't need to!
That leaf will be avenged.
O-Okay, fine.
There are five of these,
so you can have the other four.
Then we'll be even.
I knew you'd do the right thing!
Four left...
And so, this marked the beginning of a battle
to determine who'd emerge an Imperial Scholar.
We'll play one round of Old Maid.
The loser doesn't get to have a macaron.
Okay, bring it on!
I've never heard of this before.
I don't know how to play.
Are you serious?
It's simple. You just need to match
the same numbers and avoid the joker.
Okie.
Fight!
Hey, give me the joker.
I'll give it to her and secure us a win!
Roger!
She hasn't even heard of Old Maid.
She doesn't deserve the Pastry of Knowledge.
Hey, it's your turn.
I have a six, a four, a ten...
You don't need to tell them, Anya.
This'll be easy.
I'll make the joker easier to grab
and move the six farther
away so she won't grab it.
Go on. Pick one.
Six!
Huh?!
That was amazing, Anya!
Th-That was just dumb luck.
Four!
Ten!
A!
Some old guy!
Yay! I got rid of all my cards!
Now, hang on! There's no way you could've won that!
Yeah! You obviously cheated!
You must've marked the cards or something!
You guys are just making excuses.
The only other possibility
would be that she can read minds!
Oh, no! They're catching on to me!
Well, we can have a rematch
if it makes you feel better.
What? You're going too easy on them, Anya!
We're starting over with a fresh set of cards!
We're changing our order, too!
And don't you dare cheat again!
I didn't.
That was close...
I need to lose the game on purpose
so they don't figure me out!
Ooh, I got the joker.
Here you go.
The joker's in the middle. Now, grab it!
I need to mess up on purpose...
Aw, man.
I accidentally grabbed the joker.
How lame!
Nice one, stupid!
It's time for my killer move...
No, Anya. You can't hit him!
Luck's not on my side.
That was close. If I got expelled,
the mission would've been over.
I need to be a cool liar like Daddy!
No problem.
I'll secure my place
by handing the joker over to him.
Take one.
Shock!
You can read her like a book.
Welp, there's a pair.
Is he able to read minds, too?!
And I'm done!
Me, too!
Oh, no. I can't get rid of the joker!
I'm done, too!
You're pretty bad at this, too, Damian.
Shut up!
You've got this, Anya!
Here I go.
This'll decide who wins.
If I just watch how she reacts,
the game is as good as mine!
I need to look as serious as possible
so he grabs the joker!
If I lose, I won't be able to eat that dessert
and become smart!
Then I'll do bad on my tests
and won't be in the same class as Becky anymore!
I'll be all alone!
All right, this must be the winning card.
Okay, here's everyone's share.
Yay! It looks so yummy!
So exciting.
Lord Damian, how could you
possibly pick the joker there?
Shut up!
She's got some nerve...
Second Son.
Want to split it with me?
N-N-No, I don't, you dummy!
I don't need those
to become an Imperial Scholar!
You need to eat it because you're stupid!
Grr.
My, how rude!
Come on, Anya.
Let's just enjoy our dessert.
Here goes!
Yum!
I'll finally be able to get a Stella!
You may now begin your quiz.
I've lost everything dear to me.
The rest of my school life is doomed to be dark.
Th-That's not true.
You have another chance at the finals.
Yeah. Plus, at least you aren't a loner like me.
These tests seem quite difficult.
I'm gonna go lay down for a bit.
Her basic academics have improved a little,
but she's still got a ways to go.
This test on literature...
She loses a lot of points
to spelling errors,
but otherwise, she would've gotten a good score.
But she's barely studied classic literature so far.
Could she be more acquainted with it
due to her upbringing?
There aren't many countries where
people still talk like that, though.
In any case, I shouldn't
concern myself with this.
Hey, Anya. I made you
Salisbury steak for dinner.
Salisbury!
And I tried making some dessert!
Bworf?!
Here's a fake ID to get into
Doust Industries' 2nd Section.
And here are the test results for the
engine on their new fighter jet.
Thanks, once again.
Y'know, I am charging you for these.
What about the visual data on
the members of that one group?
Oh, yeah. About that...
You'll have to wait a bit longer.
One of my contacts who knew about them was offed.
The State Security Service?
I'm not completely sure,
but there are rumors that Garden got him.
Garden?
The group of assassins who have
been in this country for ages?
Aren't they basically just an urban legend?
Nah, they definitely exist.
They eliminate one traitor after another
on the shadow government's orders.
It wouldn't be out of line for Ostania to have an unofficial paramilitary organization.
You dumbass! They're not the types
you should be taking lightly.
A single assassin is capable of taking down
an entire military troop!
Don't be ridiculous. I'm counting on you.
Hold it. You gotta help me with this job
since I went the extra mile for you.
A job?
This guy.
A lost cat?
This is Kopi. He belongs to a girl named Kacey,
who works at a café I frequent.
He went missing last week,
and Kacey misses him dearly.
Twilight...
For the sake of bringing back Kacey's smile,
and while we're at it,
so that Kacey and I can get closer,
help me get this cat back.
Hey!
Hey, wait!
If you don't help me,
I'm not giving you any more intel!
Hello?!
I'll even throw in this covert
toothbrush-shaped pistol!
Damn it! He's such a heartless jerk!
Fine, I didn't need your help to get him back!
Don't go underestimating
an informant, damn it!
Hello? Jeffrey?
That's right. I've got a job for you.
I'm looking for a cat.
He's a male Nortblue, and he's
got a bell around his neck.
Let me know if you find him. Thanks.
It's been a while, Hound Joe.
You're the best guy I know for this job.
Heya, Terrance?
Yup, this is an emergency.
Hey, Nancy. You know a lot about cats, don't you?
I'd like to talk to Harrison
at the 22nd Branch Office.
Hello, Jasper.
Yo, Pat!
I saw a cat matching that description
on Ritter Street near city hall.
Excellent work, Joe.
He should be around here somewhere.
Is that you, Franky?
Yor?
Hello.
Hey.
Oh, yeah, you work at city hall, don't you?
Yes. I'm on lunch break right now.
Do you work nearby as well, Franky?
Well, no. To be honest...
There's a missing kitty?!
Oh, my goodness!
I'd love to help you.
Huh? But weren't you about to get lunch?
Oh, don't worry!
My spouse?
No, my husband's friend is in need, after all!
She's quite diligently keeping up
the wife act, isn't she?
A-As long as I won't cause you any trouble...
Sure, why not.
Of course!
So, do you know where Kopi is?
I know he's around here somewhere.
I've placed several of my cat-shaped
wiretaps, C20s, at various cat spots.
They have a sensor that's supposed to react
to the sound of the bell around Kopi's neck.
That's amazing, Franky!
Yeah, I know.
The C20 at Point A is being attacked?!
Oh, no!
It got destroyed!
How about the other points?
I guess they're getting attacked
for being outsiders.
So much for that plan.
I didn't realize that cats could be so savage...
Then we'll just have to bring him to us!
Time for the CAT-N.I.P decoy system!
Ooh!
We'll lead him to us
by spreading the smell of catnip!
Wow, you have so many clever tricks
up your sleeve, Franky!
Are you a craftsman?
Huh? I'm just a young man who
dreams of making the world
a better place with the inventions I create,
and also getting rich off of patents.
My, that's lovely!
I can't tell her that I actually
do pretty shady work.
Oh, dear...
Oh, shit! There's too many of them!
Which one of them is Kopi?!
There! The gray one!
Huh? Huh?! Which one is he?!
I'm gonna catch you, no matter what!
Please help me!
Hyper Long Hand! Take this!
Damn it, this isn't gonna work!
I need to be more direct!
Hey, get outta there!
My camera-shaped net launcher!
Kopi is definitely on his guard.
I'll carefully approach him
like I'm just trying to take a picture...
But since this looks like a camera,
the range on it is super short.
I need to get within two meters
to make sure it catches him!
Get back here, you!
Oh, that must be Kopi!
All right, Kopi. Now you've pissed me off.
There's no going back now.
This is the ultimate weapon
that I spent ten years developing!
This should give me
superhuman powers! Allegedly.
The Exo-Skeleton Power Suit!
Your days are numbered, Kopi!
This takes about 15 minutes to warm up
before it's usable,
so just stay there until then.
Hey! You're running towards
a major street, you idiot!
Stop! I'm sorry,
I won't chase you around anymore!
Franky, I'm going to borrow this for a sec...
Hi-yah!
I caught him!
I caught him, Franky!
U-Uh... Thanks.
Ten years... Ten years of my life...
Isn't this wonderful, Kopi?
You get to go home now!
But then again...
It's a small price to pay if it
gets Kacey to look my way.
Wait for me, my honey!
Thank you so much, Franky!
Oh, Kopi! I was just so worried!
That's great, babe.
This wouldn't have happened
if you didn't leave the front door open, Mark!
Look, I'm sorry.
How about I buy you those matching rings
you wanted?
Uh, yeah. This is great, yup.
Well, I'll be going now.
Seriously, thank you so much, Franky!
Live happily ever after, you two.
And so, he instead decided to live for his job.
It's such a nice feeling to help another person.
You seem happy, Yor.
Oh, why's that?
Did your hubby buy you something?
Huh? Oh, no.
Congrats on your happy marriage or whatever.
God, you piss me off.
She must've learned how to be normal.
Normal...
Am I normal?!
Huh?
Oh, thank goodness!
I'm glad I can pull off this act.
Hey, Sharon. Don't let her get too cocky.
Er... I was being sarcastic.
Hey, Briar.
Or rather, Forger. You've got a phone call.
Yes, sir! I am indeed Mrs. Forger!
It's from your usual client.
Yes, how can I serve you?
Hello.
You've got a customer, Briar Rose.