While some people liken it to a river,
others claim it's a stream of milk.
Can anyone here tell me
where this faint white glow comes from?
On a clear night,
when you look at the night sky,
our galaxy looks like one great river.
While some people liken it to a river,
others claim it's a stream of milk.
Can anyone here tell me
where this faint white glow comes from?
Me!
Me! Me! Me! Me!
Me! Me! Me!
Giovanni.
Yes, sir.
If you look at the galaxy through
a telescope, what does it look like?
Giovanni was sleeping!
Same as always.
He was late to school today.
I think he was delivering papers.
Campanella, then.
Yes, sir.
What's Campanella doing?
What's with him?
I saw Giovanni run by my house today.
He was playing with Campanella's dog.
Maybe Campanella is ignoring him,
so he has to settle for some mutt.
All right. Sit down, the both of you.
If you were to look at our
galaxy through a telescope,
you would see that it is made of stars.
Right, Giovanni?
Campanella only kept quiet so that Giovanni
wouldn't look stupid in front of the class.
But I knew the answer. Campanella and I both knew.
We had both looked at his father's
Galaxy Atlas in the den of his house.
...and if we extend
the comparison further,
these stars are like
little drops of fat floating in milk.
With that in mind...
Ever since his father went missing,
Giovanni's been struggling in class.
Isn't his dad coming back soon?
No way! He went out to capture
otters in the North Sea,
but he was caught and thrown in jail!
Zanelli!
I was going to discuss the
tremendous size of the galaxy
and the various types of stars in it,
but it seems we're out of time for today.
We'll talk about it in my next lecture.
Remember, the Festival of Stars is tonight!
I encourage everyone to take part
in the celebration.
And so, I hope to see you there!
Let's meet by the aspen trees at the school gate!
Your father gave us this crab specimen as a gift.
Hold it for me, would you?
Your father also gave us the antlers
and those rare fossils you see here.
Anyways, have you heard from your father recently?
No.
I see.
Well, stay strong.
I'll try.
I have some errands
to run on your side of town tomorrow.
I'll stop by your house
and see how your mother's doing.
Goodbye, sir.
Until next time.
Seems like your friends are making lanterns
to float on the river for the festival.
Yeah, but I won't be able to...
Oh, right. You have to work.
But maybe if I do my work quickly,
I can go to the river and watch afterwards.
Best of luck with that.
Thanks!
Yeah! I know how to make them!
Where should we meet?
Near the steps by the river!
Let's use blue candles!
It'll be easy! My father showed me how to do it!
Then you're in charge.
But do it before the festival.
We can start at Campanella's
then walk to the town commons!
Can I bring my little sister?
Sorry I'm late.
Hello, sir.
Do you have any work for me?
Can you set this up?
Yes.
Hey there, shrimp.
Keep up the good work!
Excuse me, sir. I finished.
Thank you.
I need to keep my ticket safe.
I wouldn't be able to board the train without it.
Excuse me...
Sugar and a loaf of bread, please.
Here. A loaf of bread and cube sugar.
Thank you.
Here's your change.
I'm home now, Mom.
How are you feeling?
Is that you, Giovanni? I'm glad you're home.
I felt much better today. The weather was so cool.
I got some sugar to put in your milk.
I thought you'd like that.
When did Sis get home?
Around 3 o'clock.
She tidied up the place for me.
Was your milk not delivered today?
Now that you mention it, it wasn't.
I'll go and pick it up for you.
It's okay, I'm in no rush.
Go ahead and eat first.
Your sister made tomato soup.
There should be some leftovers somewhere over there.
Okay. I'll have a little then.
Hey, Mom...
I feel like Dad'll be back any day now.
Yes. I think so too.
This morning I read some of the papers
I was delivering.
They said the fishing was
really good in the north this year.
Well, your father might not have gone fishing.
I'm sure he did. He wouldn't
do anything illegal.
You know that he isn't like that.
Like, all those other times when...
he gave small gifts to the school,
like that crab shell, and the antlers.
The school still has them on display.
Your father promised to bring you
an otter-skin coat, didn't he?
The kids at school always
bring that up to try and bother me.
Are they bullying you?
Campanella's still nice to me, at least.
Campanella's father and your father
have been friends ever since they were kids.
Dad used to take me over to
Campanella's house to play sometimes.
Things were nice back then.
You know Campanella has a wonderful
toy steam train that runs on alcohol.
Isn't the Festival of Stars tonight?
Yeah. I'm going to the festival after
I get your milk from the dairy.
Good. Have fun.
Stay away from the river, okay?
I'll watch from the shore.
I'll be back in an hour or so.
Take your time.
As long as you're with Campanella, I'll be fine.
All right, I'll stick with him.
In that case, maybe I'll stay out
for an hour and a half.
Zanelli!
Are you going to the town commons?
How's that otter-skin coat coming along, Giovanni?
Why is he always like this?
While this may resemble a stream of milk,
it is actually where our galaxy resides.
Here, where we live, exists among the stars
like drops of fat floating in milk.
You could even say that we all live
in the waters of the river of heaven...
The Centaurus Festival! It's up ahead!
Let's go!
Oh yeah, I was supposed to get milk for Mom.
Hello.
Hello?
Excuse me, we didn't get our milk today,
so I'm here to pick it up.
So, I'd like to pick up our milk.
No one's here right now.
Come back tomorrow.
I'm sorry, but I really need to get it tonight!
Are you afraid you're going to miss the train?
No, but my mother's sick
and she really needs it tonight.
I see. Well, come back a little later.
Hey, Giovanni! I can't wait to see
your new otter-skin coat!
We can't wait to see your new otter-skin coat!
Oh, dear. Is he okay?
Every light up there
in that glowing band is actually a star.
Galaxy Station! Galaxy Station!
Campanella!
The others tried following me,
but they were just too late.
Even Zanelli.
He ran as fast as he could...
but he wasn't fast enough.
Are they waiting for you somewhere?
Zanelli's already gone home.
His father came by to get him.
What's that?
It looks like your coat
got wet with dew or something.
Darn it! I must have dropped my canteen somewhere.
But that's okay.
Swan Station is coming up soon.
I love observing swans.
I can spot them from miles away,
as they glide across the river.
What a neat map!
Where did you get it?
It looks like it's made out of obsidian!
I got it at the Galaxy Station.
Didn't you get one?
I don't really remember
being at the Galaxy Station.
Hey, this spot is where we are right now, isn't it?
Yeah.
The riverbed is shining in the moonlight.
That's not moonlight!
It's the glow of the galaxy.
What is it?
I didn't think we'd get a chance
to go off on our own tonight.
Are you saying you thought
we'd be with everyone from school?
Not exactly. It doesn't matter, anyway.
Look, these must be the fields of heaven!
This train doesn't burn coal, does it?
It must run on alcohol or electricity.
Look, the gentian flowers are blooming.
It's finally autumn...
I'm going to jump out
and pick some of them!
I promise I'll be right back, okay?
You missed your chance. They're too far away now.
Hey...
I hope my mother forgives me for this.
We're probably a really long way from home now.
I hope Mom isn't worrying about me.
You know, I would do anything
in the world to make my mother happy.
But sometimes I wonder if there's something
I could do to give her true happiness.
I'm sure your mother is happy.
Why do you think she wouldn't be?
I don't know how to explain it...
But I think people are happiest
when they do something truly good.
That's why I think my mother
will forgive me for what I've done.
It looks like we'll be at Swan Station soon!
We'll arrive at exactly 11 o'clock.
Wanna go explore outside?
Let's walk around a little bit.
What a huge station!
Where'd everyone go? There's no one here.
Good question.
Where should we go?
Straight ahead!
All right, let's go!
What is it?
There's a tiny door there.
Should we open it?
Why not?
It goes on for a while. Think we should go down?
Let's do it.
It's a town commons.
Nobody's here, either.
Looks like it.
Something's written over there.
"This way to the Pliocene Coast."
Let's check it out!
These look like the steps by our river.
How far down do you think it goes?
I don't know.
Every grain of sand is a crystalline jewel.
There's a small ember inside each grain.
There's someone over there!
Let's follow them!
What is it?
It's a walnut!
Just look, they're everywhere!
That's a big one!
It's twice as big as a normal walnut.
And it's in perfect shape!
Let's go check that out!
I think they're digging something up.
Remember, be careful near that outcropping!
Use the shovel!
You'd better dig a little farther back!
Careful, careful! You're being too rough!
Are you here to observe?
Yes!
I see there that you have
found yourself a walnut!
There are tons of them around here.
That walnut dates back to 1.2 million years ago.
Over a million years?
This beach is 1.2 million years old.
That dates it to shortly after the Tertiary era.
Be careful with that chisel! Not so hard!
We've carving out an ancient animal called a vos,
which was the ancestor of our modern cow.
Will you put it on display?
No, this is purely for the sake of research.
To us, this looks like a thick,
rich, fossil stratum.
There's plenty of evidence
indicating that it's 1.2 million years old.
To others, this region might
look completely different.
It all depends on
who might be looking at it.
To someone else, this whole area
might appear to be air, water,
or an empty patch of sky.
Do you understand? Still...
Hey, stop! Don't use the shovel there!
That ground is too soft!
Understood!
It's time to go!
But I want to see a little more.
We can't. We'll miss the train if we stay.
Let's go!
Thanks a lot!
Very well then. Goodbye.
What? The whole town has changed.
Everything turned to stone.
Hurry!
We just had a sneak peek
of 1.2 million years of history!
That was amazing.
Wow, a whole 1.2 million years...
Is it okay if I take a seat here?
Yes, that's fine.
Thank you for the help, young man.
Where are you two headed off to?
To the end of the universe!
I see. Good for you!
This train can actually take you there.
And where is it that you're heading to?
I'll be getting off promptly. I'm a birdcatcher,
so I'm going to catch birds at the next stop.
What do you do with the birds
after you catch them?
You eat them. Haven't you tried bird before?
Here, try some. I just caught these herons yesterday.
People really eat these?
Sure. I get orders for them every day.
Who in the world could eat a heron?
Everyone eats them!
Here, why don't you try some yourself?
Here you go.
And some for you, too.
Don't be shy.
Well, go on!
Oh, it's candy!
Why don't you try it, too?
Sure. Thanks a lot.
What magnificent herons!
Thank you very much.
Say, what do you think about
the migratory flocks this year?
They're excellent this year.
There are hordes of birds
coming in from all over!
Just a couple of days ago,
I got some complaint calls.
I was getting calls left and right,
saying that I shouldn't mess with the light in the lighthouse.
I told them I wasn't
doing any such thing.
There were huge flocks of birds in front
of the light, one right after another!
I told those idiots,
"If you wanna complain, then complain
to the big one who leads the flock."
"He's easy to spot: long legs,
a huge beak, and a rustling cape!"
Yeah, that's what I told them.
Ah, this is my stop.
Hey, he's out there!
Ah, that was refreshing!
There's nothing more satisfying
than hard work at a job you do well in.
You have geese and heron.
Can you get cranes?
Sure, there's plenty of them all around.
You can hear them now. Go on.
Just listen carefully and you'll hear them.
It's the wireless operator.
Thank you.
You can use me for support.
Is this the place?
Yes. Thank you.
Is it picking anything up?
What do you hear?
It's hard to tell.
I've been picking this up for a while now,
but I can't seem to decipher it.
What does it sound like?
Would you mind transcribing it for me?
Sure.
The static is pretty bad.
"God... to... Thee... near..."
There's more static.
"Even... though... it... be... a... cross..."
"—eth... me... still... all..."
"my... song... shall... be..."
It seems like that's all there is.
Nothing but static after that.
What does it mean?
That signal has been coming in for a while now.
It just keeps repeating over and over again.
God to Thee near
even though it be a cross...
—eth me still
all my song shall be...
So what do you think it means?
I don't know.
Number 306.
It's number 306.
Number 306?
Hymn number 306.
Nearer, my God, to Thee, nearer to Thee!
Even though it be a cross that raiseth me.
Still all my song would be
nearer, my God, to Thee.
Nearer, my God, to Thee, nearer to Thee!
It's a prayer to be carried away to Heaven.
Whose prayer?
I don't know.
But they probably know,
in the observatory at Albireo.
The observatory at Albireo?
We're already leaving the Swan constellation.
You can see the observatory
at Albireo outside right now.
Of course, they probably won't
give you an answer.
Nearer, my God, to Thee, nearer to Thee!
Even though it be a cross that raiseth me.
Still all my song would be
nearer, my God, to Thee.
Nearer, my God, to Thee, nearer to Thee!
Ticket inspection!
Ticket inspection! Get your ticket ready.
May I have your tickets, please?
Here.
Your ticket, please.
Excuse me sir, did you get
this ticket in the third dimension?
I'm not really sure where I got it...
Enjoy the rest of your trip.
We will reach the Southern Cross
at precisely 3 o'clock.
We have different tickets.
Does my ticket take me where you're going?
Of course! That's an incredibly rare ticket!
This ticket even grants you entrance
to the Kingdom of Heaven!
With that ticket, you can...
Yeah, this kind of ticket should also take you
anywhere this train runs!
You must be very special indeed!
I don't understand.
Wait, are you...
I knew it.
I could tell you weren't
like the others on this train.
That's it, isn't it? You're...
Jeez, you're one lucky guy.
Eagle Station's coming up soon.
No matter where we go, we'll be together, right?
Where did that man go?
Where did he go?
I wish I had spent more time talking to him.
I kind of thought he was being a nuisance at first.
But now I feel bad.
Me, too.
What an odd place to be smelling apples.
Yeah, I smell them too.
Thank you.
The ship we were on hit a huge iceberg and sank.
I was hired as a tutor to these children.
We were traveling abroad when their
father had a business emergency.
He had to leave ahead of schedule.
We were about to join him.
It was late at night, and we could
barely see the moonlight.
The fog was incredibly thick.
Our ship hit an iceberg,
leaned over, and started to sink.
The port side lifeboats were already underwater.
There weren't enough boats for everyone.
The people around us quickly stepped aside
to open a path and let us through.
Though, there were a lot of other
women and children who weren't on a lifeboat yet
Nonetheless, these children needed
to be saved no matter what.
That's supposed to be my job.
I started to push through
groups of children in front of us.
But something got me thinking,
maybe it'd be better for these children to meet God,
together, than to live on at someone else's expense.
It would help them attain true happiness, I thought.
Going against God would be my sin to bear,
so I may as well do whatever it takes
to save these children.
And so, I continued to wade through the crowd.
But then, I saw mothers cramming their children
into the lifeboats, with one last kiss,
and fathers standing rigidly,
trying desperately to hold back their tears.
I couldn't, in good faith, continue.
I decided that we would join
and float together for as long as possible.
So I held them, and the three of us
waited for the ship to sink.
I'm not sure what happiness really is.
But if you keep to the true path no matter what,
you can climb any mountain, no matter how high.
I believe we can all reach true happiness,
one step at a time.
I agree.
The path to true happiness
is plagued with hardship.
We have to continue on,
even if we do so from the depths of our despair.
Would you care for an apple?
Oh, it's so beautiful.
Take it, I insist.
Would you folk like to share with me?
Thank you.
Where do these beautiful apples come from?
Around here, it seems to be sworn that good things
grow on their own, regardless of agriculture.
It isn't a hard job to do.
If you sow the proper seeds,
you'll find they bloom fast and plentiful.
I see.
It's true for apples and even for candy.
I just had a dream about my mother.
She was just asking me
if I wanted a nice big red apple.
Then, when I woke up, I was holding one!
Oh, we're still on the train.
What a beautiful apple!
It smells delicious.
I must have smelled it in my sleep.
Look, crows!
There's lots of them!
Those aren't crows. They're magpies, actually.
Oh, I see.
So cool...
Look! More apples!
That's hymn 306.
Those people in the forest out
there are singing in chorus.
Look! It's a cornfield!
How nice.
Hey look, here comes the station.
That's the New World Symphony.
What is it?
There was a boy outside
standing in front of a small house.
Really?
I think I know that boy.
I know him, too.
We must have met him somewhere before.
Is this where we are now?
It is.
Huh? What's with that glow?
That's the Flame of Scorpio.
I've heard a lot about it.
What's the Flame of Scorpio?
It's a scorpion that burned to death.
It was so hot that it burns to this day.
Scorpions are really bad bugs!
My teacher told me that they'll try
to sting you with their tail and you can die!
That's true, but scorpions aren't bad.
Our father once told us about the scorpion
of Baldora Field.
The scorpion survived
by preying on weaker insects.
One day, a weasel found it,
and it seemed like it would be eaten.
The scorpion tried desperately to escape,
only to end up falling in a deep well.
He thought to himself:
"How often have I preyed on other creatures?"
"And now, the one time that
I was the prey, I fled in utter terror."
"And look what came of that.
I'll die in this well, alone."
"Ah... Life is filled with uncertainty."
"I could have given the weasel
another day of life with my sacrifice."
"But now..."
"my death will help no one."
"Dear Lord, I beg of you, look into
my heart and hear my prayer."
"In my next life,
don't allow me to throw my life away in vain."
"Let me use my body for the true
happiness of everyone in the world."
And then the scorpion burst into flame.
A brilliant crimson glow.
And by the light of his burning body,
he lit up the night forever.
How beautiful.
We're at the village of Centaurus!
Centaurus! The Festival!
Oh, yeah! It's the Festival of Stars!
It looks like everyone is out celebrating
the Centaurus Festival tonight.
We'll be at the Southern Cross soon.
Time to get ready to go.
We need to get ready to go now.
I want to stay here on the train!
I know, but we have to get off here.
No! I'm staying on the train!
I want to ride some more!
I'm sorry, but we have to get off here.
This is how we get into Heaven.
Come on, time to go.
Well, then... Goodbye.
Goodbye.
I guess it's just the two of us now.
Hey, let's just keep going like this forever, okay?
That's right! We'll always be together, won't we?
Yeah. I'd like that.
But then again, where exactly are we going, anyway?
Well, I don't know.
Well, we're in this together!
Hey, look at that!
It's the Coal Sack. A hole in the sky.
Hey, don't worry! I'm not afraid of the dark anymore.
We can get through this, together.
All right. Until the end.
Look at that lovely field out there.
Where?
That must be the field of the Heavens.
I see now. That's where my mother is.
We'll always be together, won't we?
Campanella!
Campanella! Wait, I'm going with you!
Goodbye, Giovanni.
Wait!
You promised we'd be together forever!
Open up! Open up!
Campanella! Campanella!
Open up! Open up! Campanella!
Goodbye, Giovanni.
Campanella...
Campanella!
Oh, yeah! Mom's waiting on me for dinner.
Hello!
Yeah?
We didn't get our milk today.
Oh, I'm terribly sorry.
I'm afraid I left the calf's gate open
this afternoon.
He went straight for his mother and drank
half her milk before I could stop him!
Here.
Oh, I see. Thank you very much.
I'm sorry about that!
It's all right.
Marceau, what's wrong?
Giovanni, hurry!
Everybody's all down by the river!
The river?
Giovanni, Campanella fell in the river!
Zanelli was standing in one of the boats
and he leaned out to
put his lantern in the water,
but the boat lurched and Zanelli
fell in and started to sink!
Campanella dove right in after him!
He swam down and pushed
Zanelli back to the boat!
Kato pulled Zanelli back to safety, but by then...
By then, Campanella had disappeared!
Everyone in town is searching for him.
His father's there, too.
But they haven't found him!
They took Zanelli home, already.
Well, he could be further downstream by now.
No. It's no use now.
It's been 45 minutes since he fell in.
In that case...
Campanella...
Giovanni, I didn't see you there.
Thanks for what you've done tonight.
I've been meaning to ask you,
has your father come home yet?
No.
I wonder what's wrong.
He seemed very happy in the letter
I got from him just a few days ago.
He should have been home today.
Maybe his boat is late.
Giovanni. If you're up for it,
you and your friends should come over
for a visit at my house sometime.
I know Campanella is out there.
He's there, at the edge of the universe.
I know because we explored it together.
I...
I vow to be like that scorpion.
For the true happiness of everyone...
I will let my body burn a hundred times over.
Campanella...
No matter where I go, we'll always be together.
The occurrence that is myself
is like the turquoise illumination
of an organic alternating-current lamp.
A compound of countless pellucid spirits.
Continuously, it shines on and on,
in unison with every other being.
It is the turquoise illumination
of an intricate alternating-current lamp.
Though the lamp will be lost,
its light will remain.
This is the product of paper and mineral ink
guided by the last 22 months of time,
and the sensations I felt during that period.
Sensations brought upon by the universe around me—
ones that every other being could also feel.
It is a mental sketch of the dark and the light
as they have remained with me until today.