The fireworks will begin shortly.
We hope everyone is able to join us
as we light up the sky.
Let's end the cruise with a bang!
For now, let's head to the third cargo room,
where the inflatable boats are stored.
The director is waiting for us there.
We'll lower the boat from
the emergency exit on the second deck.
Then, we'll have the rendezvous
ship retrieve you.
Ideally, this should all happen during the show.
What should we do with our extra time?
Wanna watch the fireworks?
Terrible idea. Let's hit up the casino!
I'm gonna win big and kiss city hall goodbye!
You're gonna piss off the director...
L-Let's keep our guard up as we proceed.
Y-Yeah...
Blue Lace No. 89 and Mermaid...
They're both popular perfumes.
But the combination of those two scents,
as well as the woman without a scent...
One man, two women, and a baby.
I've found you.
I love fireworks!
Do you?
Papa!
I wanna look over there, too!
I can't see with so many people around.
I wonder if we'll see Mommy around here.
I really doubt we will.
I'm so excited.
I'm going to propose to my
girlfriend at the finale.
I can't tell if she's here or not
with this much chitter chatter.
I wonder when I should tell her that she's
more beautiful than the fireworks.
I'll have to listen closely.
Those people could be assassins.
Is there any place we can avoid them?
Let's go around them.
Here too?
All the routes to the bow
are swarming with enemies.
Of course, I could try brute forcing it,
but they might call for backup.
They could also figure out
what we're planning.
Let's head back up to the deck for now.
Is everything okay?
The director gave me a key
that opens the crew corridors.
We'll sneak out using paths
unavailable to the public.
I don't sense anyone here.
Everyone's probably distracted by
the event, so we should be fine,
but try to make as little noise as possible.
Shh.
O-Okay...
Let's go.
Th-That caught me by surprise.
There, there. They're just fireworks, my love.
We can use the noise as cover. Let's go!
Up here!
Hup!
Wow.
Let's hurry over there.
I see two with black hair.
Is it the one holding the kid?
That's the one. Get the baby while you're at it, too.
Roger that.
She dodged it?!
Oh, dear... He dodged it.
Are you hurt?
I-I'm okay... I think.
Are you all right?!
I didn't feel their presence.
Whoa, hold on there...
These are all skilled assassins.
There's no escape.
You're going first, bitch. This is what you get.
Honestly...
I was wondering why you never showed up.
Director!
Tch. Guess we have more to worry about.
Get to cover, you two!
Hide under that hatch!
You're not going anywhere!
Come on, Olka!
Too slow.
Someone in my blind spot?!
Zeb!
That hurt! What a shitty good-for-nothing
bulletproof vest!
Maybe use your brain next time!
Nice going, Mr. Grey!
I can finally be at ease
knowing they're safe in there.
You think that's enough to stop me?
I'll blow you to smithereens!
Pardon me.
Tch.
Don't poke your body out!
Well, that won't do. The deck is a complete mess.
I'll need to make it look like
none of this ever happened.
You're mine—
I'd appreciate if you could do this
as bloodlessly as possible.
This is not an easy cleanup.
I didn't notice you made it down here, Director!
I'm terribly sorry. It completely slipped my mind.
Well, what's done is done.
We're up against countless trained assassins,
with unique fighting styles we've
never seen before.
Still...
They're nothing compared to Garden.
They saved us the trouble
of having to track them down.
Let's purge this filth.
Look, now they've turned red!
I don't know how you can be equally excited
by every single one that goes up.
Bravo!
No way, Vides! I hit the jackpot!
That was enough poison to take down a bear!
Goodness! You're so rude.
It is I, Esmerelda! The master of wire—
I'm the king of chak—
The fireworks show is about to reach its climax!
That hurt!
Just, "That hurt"?
And that concludes our event!
I jammed my finger...
Well, damn.
You killed every last one of them.
What a terrible person you are.
Huh? Yes, I killed them.
There wasn't much else I could've done.
Those who point their blade at another
cannot complain when they
have one pointed at them.
That includes myself.
You're so earnest. Well, no matter.
This just means I get a
bigger cut of the money.
It may be too late to ask,
but could I convince you to walk away from this?
We can still avoid needless bloodshed.
Who do you think you are?
That's not going to happen.
We've already received a down payment,
and we're stuck on this boat—much like you are.
Also, I suspect he has no intention
of letting us leave.
You're staring a hole through them, Director!
War is just another way
to get paid to these people.
These types only ever cause harm
to our country.
Sounds like an old soldier with old ideas.
You should learn a thing or two
from the West. Money is power.
Everyone's happy if we're all rich, right?
This business requires
an adequate amount of foresight.
You can take some time to self-reflect
while you're sleeping with the fishes.
I don't think I'm the one who'll end up as fish food.
Director!
My grip strength...
It's over.
You only postpone the inevitable. Give up.
He's on a different level than the others.
My legs are heavy again.
In the event that you get
seriously wounded or killed,
I will tell the Forgers that you
have been transferred.
If I disappeared without saying a word...
What an awful woman I would be.
It'll draw attention
if I suddenly have a new hairstyle!
Huh? You got a haircut on your trip?
Well, you see, it's how I dealt
with being turned down!
No, now's not the time to
be worrying about that!
At this rate, I'm going to be sliced in two!
If you fear death, I'm afraid
it is you who should withdraw, madam.
Th-That isn't happening!
I won't let you lay a finger
on Olka or the others!
Sucks being at the bottom
of the ladder, huh?
If you'll yield, I wouldn't mind giving you a cut.
I'd rather not get hurt anyway.
I don't want a cut! Don't be ridiculous!
There's nothing ridiculous about it.
It's a genuine business proposition.
You're just like us.
Killing is what puts food on the table.
Don't compare me to you! I'm—
I'm doing this to support my family...
I guess that means I am doing it for the money.
But... wait, I already make an honest wage.
I'm hunting down bad guys for my country!
For my country?
Have I always been so righteous?
What am I doing this for?
Oh, no—
Oh, dear. He might actually
kill me. What should I do?
Now I won't be able to get Loid's
shirts from the cleaners.
I also won't be able to return
Anya's library books.
Wait, what am I even saying?
Why is he pointing a giant sword at me?
My head hurts...
I think I'm a bit tired.
Yor! Hey, Yor!
Oh... Memories of when Yuri was growing up.
Yippee! Yor, I just got
a job offer from foreign affairs!
Oh, Yuri... I'm so proud of you.
I bought you this with my first paycheck!
You don't need me to support you anymore.
Oh, my!
I don't need to kill for a living anymore.
That's right.
Let's finish this.
After all, if I die, I won't be able
to go to the cleaners or the library.
It's over. Finish off Olka and the others.
Got it.
Stop... right there.
What are you doing?
Olka?
Olka. Why was I acting
as her bodyguard again?
I just want to live a quiet, peaceful life.
That's right.
The reason I started this job...
and continued this job...
Life had gotten so hectic that
I had completely forgotten.
Was it for the money? For my country?
That's only how I justified it.
All I wanted
was to protect his innocence.
There are so many
needless tragedies in the world.
To make sure I don't add to them...
To reduce that number by even one...
I have to make the world a beautiful place.
And I stand by that.
In fact, I have more to lose than ever before.
I don't need peace.
I don't care how much blood I've spilled.
Even if my life is constantly on the line...
Even if I have to leave the Forgers...
Enduring a merciless job,
be it for a loved one or for any other reason,
requires an incredible amount of dedication.
And that's something to be proud of.
I'm sure Loid would appreciate this.
He'd understand.
I have no reason...
to give up!
He fled to the back alley!
Go around and cut him off, Yuri!
Roger!
What's wrong, Yuri?!
Did the suspect get you?!
Sir... it appears that...
I caught a cold.
So suddenly?!
I've never seen you get sick before.
When I...
When I remember that my sister isn't here,
my immune system breaks down.
Oh, right. She's on a business
trip right now, isn't she?
On that cruise.
I'm sorry I let the suspect get away.
Just get some rest.
I'm going to the drug store.
Oh, wait...
Could you also get me some herbal tea?
The one with the bear on it.
Fine.
Whenever I get a cold,
it reminds me of when I was a kid...
Oh, no! You have a fever, Yuri!
What should I do? What should I do?
Don't worry about me, Yor.
I'll be fine if I get some rest.
First things first, I've gotta get you warm!
I'll use every blanket we have!
That's too many, Yor!
Apparently in the east,
they wrap green onions around their necks!
I give! Yor, I give up!
Nothing beats herbal tea
with some honey when you're sick!
Try putting elderflower or sage in it.
Thanks, Mrs. Nabor!
I'm heading to the mountains now!
I'm home, Yuri!
These should help out with your fever!
Yor?! What in the world happened to you?!
I accidentally made
some bees mad, tee-hee.
Oh, and I also fought a boar.
Let's make you some hotpot!
And I'll make you some
herbal tea right away!
I can't let her hurt herself every time I get sick...
I need to grow up big and strong.
Hurry up and get better, Yuri!
Hey, Yor.
Hm?
I'm really glad to be your little brother.
Goodness, stop talking like you're going to die!
I'm fine.
I'm glad I have you by my side, too.
Make sure you take care of yourself, okay?
Yor...
Someone so special shouldn't
have to live in such a cruel world.
Drink this! It should help with your cold.
I will, thanks.
This sure warms you right up!
Oh, thank goodness.
There's so much going on
in my body right now
that I'm not worried about my
cold symptoms at all anymore!
Oh, thank goodness!
You all right? You wouldn't
stop moaning in your sleep.
I bought the stuff you asked for.
Thank you very much.
This stuff is famous for tasting awful.
It works the best for me.
It also tastes the most similar to
what my sister would make for me.
All right! All better!
Let's go catch that suspect!
I'm going to purify the world
before my sister gets back!
Stay in bed!